<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addons>
<addon id="metadata.album.universal"
       name="Universal Album Scraper"
       version="1.7.3"
       provider-name="Olympia, Team XBMC">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.last.fm" version="1.5.1"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.allmusic.com" version="2.5.2"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.musicbrainz.org" version="1.2.3"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.fanart.tv" version="2.1.2"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.amazon.de" version="1.0.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.theaudiodb.com" version="1.4.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.albums"
             language="en"
             library="albumuniversal.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af">Universele Skraper vir Albums</summary>
    <summary lang="be">Universal Scraper for Albums</summary>
    <summary lang="bg">Универсален източник за информация за албуми</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">Arreplegador universal per àlbums</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">Univerzální zdroj získávání dat pro alba</summary>
    <summary lang="da">Universel Scraper til Albummer</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Universeller Scraper für Alben</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Universal Scraper Άλμπουμ</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Universal Scraper for Albums</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Scraper universal para álbumes</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Scraper Universal para Albumes</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Scraper Universal para Álbumes</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">Universaali tiedonhakija albumitiedoille</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Scraper universel pour les Albums</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">Scraper universal para os álbumes</summary>
    <summary lang="he">סקרייפר אוניברסלי עבור אלבומים</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Univerzális album leolvasó</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Ricercatore Universale per Albums</summary>
    <summary lang="ja">汎用アルバムスクレーパー</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">Universal Scraper for Albums</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">Universalus Albumų Scrapers</summary>
    <summary lang="mk">Универзален превземач за Албуми</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Universele Scraper voor Albums</summary>
    <summary lang="no">Universalskraper for Albummer</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Universal Scraper dla albumów muzycznych</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Scraper universal para álbuns</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Scraper Universal para Álbuns</summary>
    <summary lang="ro"> Scraper universal pentru albume</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Универсальный скрапер для альбомов</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">Univerzálny zdroj získavania dát pre albumy</summary>
    <summary lang="sl">Univerzalni ponudnik informacij o albumih</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">Universiell albumskrapa</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">通用音乐专辑信息刮削器</summary>
    <description lang="af">Hierdie skraper kollekteer inligting vanaf die volgende ondersteunde werwe: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com en amazon.de, terwyl kunswerke gegryp word vanaf: fanart.tv, last.fm en allmusic.com. Dit kan veld vir veld gestel word vanaf watter werf jy die spesifieke inligting wil hê.&#10;&#10;Die aanvaklike soektog word altyd op MusicBrainz gedoen. Ingeval skakels van allmusic en/of amazon.de nie bygevoeg is op die MusicBrainz werf, kan velde vanaf allmusic.com en/of amazon.de nie gaan haal word nie (egter baie maklik om daardie ontbrekende skakels by te voeg).</description>
    <description lang="be">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic and/or amazon.de links are not added on the MusicBrainz site, fields from allmusic.com and/or amazon.de cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="bg">Сваля информация от следните сайтове: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com и amazon.de. Изобрания извлича от: fanart.tv, last.fm и allmusic.com. Можете да определите от кой сайт каква информация да се сваля.&#10;&#10;Първоначалното търсене винаги се прави в MusicBrainz. Когато не са налични препратки към allmusic и/или amazon.de на сайта на MusicBrainz извличането на информация от allmusic.com и/или amazon.de става невъзможно (добавянето им е много лесно).</description>
    <description lang="ca">Aquest arreplegador recull informació dels següents llocs: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com i amazon.de, alhora que agafa art de: fanart.tv, last.fm i allmusic.com. Es pot configurar camp a camp des de quin lloc voleu aquella informació específica. &#10;&#10;La cerca inicial es realitza sempre a MusicBrainz. En el cas que els enllaços d'allmusic i amazon.de no s'afegeixin al lloc MusicBrainz els camps d'allmusic i amazon.de i/o amazon.com no es poden obtenir (tot i que són fàcils d'afegir aquests enllaços restants).</description>
    <description lang="cs">Tento zdroj získává data z následujících podporovaných stránek: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, last.fm a allmusic.com. Je možno podrobně nastavit, které informace si přejete získat ze kterých stránek.&#10;&#10;Prvotní vyhledání je vžy provedeno na MusicBrainz. V případě, že odkaz pro allmusic a nebo amazon.de není přidaný na stránku MusicBrainz, není možné údaje z allmusic.com a amazon.de stáhnout (avšak je velmi snadné tyto chybějící odkazy přidat).</description>
    <description lang="da">Denne scraper samler information fra følgende sider: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com og amazon.de og henter illustrationer fra: fanart.tv, last.fm og allmusic.com. Det kan vælges felt for felt, hvilke sider du ønsker, at få den pågældende information fra.&#10;&#10;Den første søgning er altid på MusicBrainz. Hvis ikke allmusic og/eller amazon.de linkene er tilføjet på MusicBrainz side, kan felter fra allmusic.com og/eller amazon.de ikke hentes (men det er helt enkelt at tilføje de manglende links).</description>
    <description lang="de">Dieser Scaper sammelt Informationen von den folgenden unterstützten Seiten: MusicBrainz, Last.fm, Allmusic.com und Amazon.de und lädt dabei Grafiken von: Fanart.tv, Last.fm und Allmusic.com. Es kann eingestellt werden, von welcher Seite die spezifischen Informationen stammen.⏎ ⏎ Die initialie Suche wird immer über MusicBrainz durchgeführt. Sollten keine Allmusic- und/oder Amazon.de-Links auf der MusicBrainz-Seite gesetzt worden sein, können Felder von Allmusic.com und/oder Amazon.de nicht geladen werden (fehlende Links können jedoch sehr einfach hinzugefügt werden).</description>
    <description lang="el">Αυτό το scraper συλλέγει πληροφορίες από τις ακόλουθες υποστηριζόμενες ιστοσελίδες: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com και amazon.de, ενώ λαμβάνει εικόνες από τα: fanart.tv, last.fm και allmusic.com. Μπορεί να οριστεί πεδίο ανά πεδίο αναλόγως των πληροφοριών που επιθυμείτε από την εκάστοτε ιστοσελίδα.&#10;&#10;Η αρχική αναζήτηση γίνεται πάντα στο MusicBrainz. Σε περίπτωση που δεν έχουν προστεθεί σύνδεσμοι για το allmusic ή/και το amazon.de στο MusicBrainz, δε θα μπορούν να ληφθούν πεδία από το allmusic.com ή/και το amazon.de (ωστόσο είναι πολύ εύκολο να προστεθούν αυτοί οι ελλιπείς σύνδεσμοι).</description>
    <description lang="en">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic and/or amazon.de links are not added on the MusicBrainz site, fields from allmusic.com and/or amazon.de cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="es">Este scraper recolecta información de las siguientes webs: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com y amazon.de, mientras obtiene las imágenes de fanart.tv, last.fm y allmusic.com. Permite especificar de qué web se quiere obtener la información para cada campo. ⏎ ⏎ La búsqueda inicial se realiza siempre en MusicBrainz. En caso de que los enlaces a allmusic y/o amazon.de no estén añadidos en la web de MusicBrainz, no se podrán obtener los campos de información de estos dos sitios (aunque es muy fácil añadir esos enlaces que faltan).</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">Este scraper recolecta información de las siguientes webs: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com y amazon.de, mientras obtiene las imágenes de fanart.tv, last.fm y allmusic.com. Permite especificar de qué web se quiere obtener la información para cada campo. ⏎ ⏎ La búsqueda inicial se realiza siempre en MusicBrainz. En caso de que los enlaces a allmusic y/o amazon.de no estén añadidos en la web de MusicBrainz, no se podrán obtener los campos de información de estos dos sitios (aunque es muy fácil añadir esos enlaces que faltan).</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">Este scraper obtiene información de los siguientes sitios soportados: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com y amazon.de, mientras obtiene artwork de: fanart.tv, last.fm y allmusic.com. Puede ser configurado campo por campo de que sitio quieres esa información específica.⏎ ⏎ La búsqueda inicial siempre es hecha en MusicBrainz. En el caso en que los enlaces de allmusic y/o amazon.de no son agregados en el sitio de  MusicBrainz, campos de allmusic.com y/o amazon.de no pueden ser obtenidos. (De cualquier manera es muy fácil agregar esos enlaces no encontrados).</description>
    <description lang="fi">Tämä tiedonhakija käyttää tietolähteinään seuraavia sivustoja:MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com ja amazon.de. Kuvat ja grafiikat haetaan seuraavilta sivustoilta: fanart.tv, last.fm ja allmusic.com. Voit määrittää tarkasti, miltä sivustoilta mitäkin tietoa haetaan.&#10;&#10;Ensimmäinen haku tehdään aina lähteestä MusicBrainz. Mikäli allmusic- ja/tai amazon.de-linkkejä ei ole lisätty MusicBrainz-sivustolle, haku ei onnistu (mutta puuttuvien linkkien lisääminen on helppoa).</description>
    <description lang="fr">Ce collecteur utilise les informations des sites suivant : MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com et amazon.de et télécharge les artwork depuis : fanart.tv, last.fm et allmusic.com. Vous pouvez spécifier quel site utiliser pour chaque information à employer.&#10;&#10;Le premier résultat est toujours en provenance de MusicBrainz. Dans le cas où allmusic et/ou amazon.de ne sont pas ajoutés sur le site MusicBrainz, les champs de allmusic.com et/ou amazon.de ne peuvent pas être traités (il est toutefois très simple d'ajouter ces liens manquants).</description>
    <description lang="gl">Este scraper obtén a información dende os seguintes sitios soportados: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com e amazon.de, mentres que as ilustracións as obtén dende: fanart.tv, last.fm e allmusic.com. Pódese definir dende que sitios se obterá a información específica de cada campo.&#10;&#10;A busca inicial faise sempre en MusicBrainz. No caso de non estar engadidas as ligazón de allmusic e/ou amazon.de no sitio de MusicBrainz, os campos de allmusic.com e/ou amazon.de non se poderán obter (aínda que é moi doado de engadir as ligazóns).</description>
    <description lang="he">סקרייפר זה אוסף מידע מהתארים הנתמכים הבאים: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, בעוד שמשיכת גרפיקה נעשית דרך: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. יש אפשרות להגדיר את זאת שדה אחר שדה מאיזה אתר ברצונך למשוך את המידע הספציפי.⏎ ⏎ החיפוש הפנימי נעשה תמיד דרך MusicBrainz. במקרה שקישור allmusic לא התווסף באתר MusicBrainz, השדות מאת allmusic.com אינן יכולות להימשך (למרות שזה מאוד קל להוסיף את הקישורים הריקים).</description>
    <description lang="hu">A leolvasó szöveges infókat gyűjt a támogatott oldalakról: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, valamint képeket a : fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com-ról. Beállítható hogy honnan, és milyen infót gyűjtsön. A keresés mindig a MusicBrainz-on folyik, de könnyen hozzáadhatjuk a hiányzó találatokat az allmusic.com, vagy az amazon.de-ről.</description>
    <description lang="it">Questo ricercatore prende informazioni dai seguenti siti: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com e amazon.de, mentre prende grafica da: fanart.tv, last.fm e allmusic.com. Puoi impostare campo per campo cosa prendere e da dove.⏎ ⏎La ricerca iniziale viene sempre fatta su MusicBrainz. In caso i links a allmusic e/o amazon.de non sono stati messi su MusicBrainz, i campi da questi siti non possono essere recuperati (è molto facile aggiungere quei link, comunque).</description>
    <description lang="ja">このスクレーパーは、以下のサイトから情報を取得します：MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com, amazon.de。アートワークは以下のサイトから取得します：fanart.tv, last.fm, allmusic.com。各フィールドごとに、どの情報をどのサイトから取得するか、個別に指定することもできます。&#10;&#10;最初は MusicBrainz を使って検索が行われます。MusicBrainz サイトに allmusic や amazon.de のリンクが追加されていない場合は、allmusic.com / amazon.de からのフィールドは取得できません (リンクを追加するのは簡単ですが)。</description>
    <description lang="ko">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic and/or amazon.de links are not added on the MusicBrainz site, fields from allmusic.com and/or amazon.de cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="lt">Šis Scrapers renka informaciją iš šių palaikomų svetainių: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com ir/arba amazon.de, o scrap meno kūrinius iš: fanart.tv, last.fm ir/arba allmusic.com. Jis gali būti nustatytas srities lauke, iš kurio puslapio norite, kad konkrečią informaciją paimtu. Pradinė paieška visada atliekama remiantis MusicBrainz. Jei Allmusic ir/ar amazon.de nuorodos nėra įdėtos MusicBrainz svetainėje, laukuose allmusic.com ir/arba amazon.de negali būti realūs (nors įtraukti tas trūkstamas grandis labai lengva).</description>
    <description lang="mk">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.⏎ ⏎ The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic and/or amazon.de links are not added on the MusicBrainz site, fields from allmusic.com and/or amazon.de cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="nl">Deze scraper verzamelt informatie van de volgende ondersteunde sites: MusicBrainz, Last.fm, allmusic.com en amazon.de. Afbeeldingen worden verzameld van de volgende sites: fanart.tv, Last.fm en allmusic.com. Per veld kan aangegeven worden van welke site je de specifieke informatie wil halen. De initiële zoekopdracht wordt altijd gedaan van MusicBrainz. In het geval dat links naar allmusic en/of amazon.de niet zijn toegevoegd op de MusicBrainz site, kunnen velden niet worden opgehaald bij deze sites. (Het is niet moeilijk om de ontbrekende links toe te voegen.)</description>
    <description lang="no">Denne skraperen samler informasjon fra følgende støttede steder: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com og amazon.de, mens den henter artwork fra: fanart.tv, last.fm og allmusic.com. Du kan stegvis velge hvilken kilde du ønsker å hente spesifikk informasjon fra.&#10;&#10;Det første søket er alltid gjort hos MusicBrainz. I tilfeller hvor allmusic og/eller amazon.de linker ikke er lagt til hos MusicBrainz siden, kan ikke felter fra allmusic.com og/eller amazon.de hentes (det er veldig lett å legge til de manglende linkene).</description>
    <description lang="pl">Ten scraper zbiera informacje z następujących stron: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com oraz amazon.de, a grafiki pobiera z: fanart.tv, last.fm i allmusic.com. Dla każdego pola z informacjami można wybrać osobną stronę.&#10;&#10;Początkowe wyszukiwanie jest zawsze wykonywane na MusicBrainz. Gdy linki do allmusic i/lub amazon.de nie są dodane na stronie MusicBrainz, nie można pobrać tych pól z allmusic.com i/lub amazon.de (pomimo to brakujące linki można bardzo łatwo dodać).</description>
    <description lang="pt">Este scraper recolhe informações dos seguintes sítios:&#10;MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com e amazon.de, enquanto obtém artwork de: fanart.tv, last.fm e allmusic.com. Pode definir em cada campo o sítio do qual quer obter as informações. A pesquisa inicial é sempre feita no MusicBrainz. Caso os links allmusic e/ou amazon.de não tenham sido adicionados no sítio MusicBrainz, os campos do allmusic.com e/ou amazon.de não serão obtidos (no entanto, é muito fácil adicionar os links em falta). </description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Este scraper coleta informações nos seguintes sites:&#10;MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com e amazon.de, enquanto pega os artwork de: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. O Mesmo pode ser configurara campo a campo em que site você quer obter informações específicas. A procura inicial é sempre feita no MusicBrainz. No caso allmusic e/ou amazon.de não terem sido adicionados no site MusicBrainz, campos de allmusic.com e/ou amazona.de não serão buscados (embora seja muito fácil adicionar os links faltantes). </description>
    <description lang="ro">Acest scraper colectează informații de la următoarele site-uri suportate: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com și amazon.de. Elementele de grafica sunt accesate din: fanart.tv, last.fm și allmusic.com. Acesta poate fi setat câmp cu câmp de pe care site doriți informațiile specifice sa fie colectate ⏎ ⏎ Căutarea inițială se face întotdeauna pe MusicBrainz. În cazul în care Allmusic și / sau link-ul amazon.de nu sunt adăugate pe MusicBrainz, câmpurile din allmusic.com și / sau amazon.de nu pot fi colectate (este foarte ușor însă de adăugat aceste legături lipsă).</description>
    <description lang="ru">Данный скрапер собирает информацию со следующих сайтов:&#10;MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com и amazon.de, при этом получая обложки из: fanart.tv, last.fm и allmusic.com. Каждое поле можно настроить так, чтобы оно получало желаемую информацию с определенного вами сайта.⏎ ⏎ Начальный поиск всегда проводится на  MusicBrainz. Для allmusic и/или amazon.de ссылки на сайт MusicBrainz отсутствуют, поля с allmusic.com и/или amazon.de не могут быть заполнены (добавить пропущенные ссылки очень просто).</description>
    <description lang="sk">Tento zdroj získavania dát zbiera informácie z nasledujúcich podporovaných stránok: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com a amazon.de, zatiaľ čo umeleckú grafiku získava zo stránok: fanart.tv, last.fm a allmusic.com. Je možné podrobne nastaviť, z ktorej stránky chcete získať konkrétne informácie.&#10;&#10;Počiatočné hľadanie je vždy na stránke MusicBrainz. V prípade, že odkaz pre allmusic a/alebo amazon.de nie je pridaný na stránku MusicBrainz, nie je možné získať údaje zo stránky allmusic.com a/alebo amazon.de (je ale veľmi jednoduché tieto chýbajúce odkazy pridať).</description>
    <description lang="sl">Ta ponudnik združuje informacije s sledečih strani: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com in amazon.de; grafike prenaša z: fanart.tv, last.fm in allmusic.com. Vsako informacijo lahko prenesete z različne strani.&#10;&#10;Začeno iskanje je vedn na MusicBrainz. V primeru, da na MusicBrainz ni povezave do allmusic.com in/ali amazon.de, informacij od tam ne morete prenesti (a to težavo hitro lahko odpravite).</description>
    <description lang="sv">Denna skrapa samlar information från följande sajter: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com och amazon.de, och konstverk från: fanart.tv, last.fm och allmusic.com. Det kan anges fält för fält vilken sajt du vill få den specifika informationen.⏎ ⏎ Den initiala sökningen är alltid utförd på MusicBrainz sajt, fälten från allmusic.com och/eller amazon.de länkarna läggs inte till på MusicBrainz sajten, fälten från allmusic.com och/eller amazon.de kan inte hämtas (väldigt enkelt att lägga till dom saknade länkarna dock).</description>
    <description lang="zh">本刮削器支持从以下网站获取信息：MusicBrainz、last.fm、allmusic.com和amazon.de，并从以下网站获取艺术图片：fanart.tv、last.fm和allmusic.com。你可以指定每一项内容的来源网站。&#10;&#10;初始结果总是先从MusicBrainz获取。如果MusicBrainz网站没有到allmusic和/或amazon.de的外部链接，则无法获取allmusic.com的/或amazon.de的信息（当然你能很容易地加入缺失的链接）。</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="metadata.artists.universal"
       name="Universal Artist Scraper"
       version="2.6.3"
       provider-name="Olympia, Team XBMC">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.last.fm" version="1.6.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.allmusic.com" version="2.6.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.musicbrainz.org" version="1.3.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.htbackdrops.com" version="1.2.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.fanart.tv" version="2.1.2"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.theaudiodb.com" version="1.5.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.artists"
             language="en"
             library="artistuniversal.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af">Universal Skraper vir Kunstenaars</summary>
    <summary lang="be">Universal Scraper for Artists</summary>
    <summary lang="bg">Универсален източник за информация за артисти</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">Arreplegador universal per artistes</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">Univerzální zdroj získávání dat pro umělce</summary>
    <summary lang="da">Universel Scraper til Kunstnere</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Universal Scraper für Interpreten</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Universal Scraper Καλλιτεχνών</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Universal Scraper for Artists</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Scraper universal para artistas</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Scraper Universal para Artistas</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Scraper Universal de Artistas</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">Universaali artistien tiedonhakija</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Collecteur universel d'artistes</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">Scraper Universal para Artistas</summary>
    <summary lang="he">Universa סקרייפר אמנים</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Univerzális előadó leolvasó</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Scraper universale degli artisti</summary>
    <summary lang="ja">汎用アーティストスクレーパー</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">Universal Scraper for Artists</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">Universalus Artistų Scrapers</summary>
    <summary lang="mk">Universal Scraper for Artists</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Universele scraper voor artiesten</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Universal Scraper dla Artystów muzycznych</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Scraper universal para Artistas</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Scraper Universal para Artistas</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Scraper universal pentru artisti</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Универсальный скрапер для исполнителей</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">Univerzálny zdroj získavania dát pre umelcov</summary>
    <summary lang="sl">Univerzalen ponudnik informacij o izvajalcih</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">Universiell artistskrapa</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">通用艺术家信息刮削器</summary>
    <description lang="af">Hierdie skraper versamel informasie van die volgende ondersteunde werwe: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, en allmusic.com, terwyl kunswerke gryp van: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm en allmusic.com. Dit kan veld vir veld gestel word vanaf watter werf jy die spesifike informasie wil hê.&#10;&#10;Die aanvanklike soektog word altyd op MusicBrainz gedoen. Ingeval die allmusic skakel nie bygevoeg is op die MusicBrainz werf, kan velde van allmusic.com nie gaan haal word nie (egter baie maklik om daardie ontbrekende skakels by te voeg).</description>
    <description lang="be">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic link is not added on the MusicBrainz site fields from allmusic.com cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="bg">Сваля информация от следните сайтове: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com. Изобрания извлича от: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. Можете да определите от кой сайт каква информация да се сваля.&#10;&#10;Първоначалното търсене винаги се прави в MusicBrainz. Когато не е налична препратка към allmusic.com на сайта на MusicBrainz извличането на информация от allmusic.com става невъзможно (добавянето на препратка е много лесно).</description>
    <description lang="ca">Aquest arreplegador recull informació dels següents llocs suportats</description>
    <description lang="cs">Tento zdroj dat získává informace z následujících podporovaných stránek: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm a allmusic.com. Lze nastavit jakou informaci stahovat z jakých stránek.&#10;&#10;Základní hledání je vždy provedeno na MusicBrainz. V případě, že schází odkaz allmusic na stránce MusicBrains, nelze stáhnout informace z allmusic.com (avšak je velmi snadné chybějící odkazy přidat).</description>
    <description lang="da">Denne scraper samler information fra følgende sider: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, og allmusic.com, og henter illustrationer fra: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm og allmusic.com. Det kan vælges felt for felt, fra hvilke sider du ønsker, at få de pågældende informationer fra.&#10;&#10;Den første søgning er altid på MusicBrainz. Hvis ikke allmusic linket er tilføjet på MusicBrainz side, kan felter fra allmusic.com ikke hentes (men det er helt enkelt at tilføje de manglende links).</description>
    <description lang="de">Dieser Scraper unterstützt das Sammeln von Informationen von den folgenden Seiten: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, und allmusic.com, Grafiken werden geladen von: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm und allmusic.com. Es kann Feld für Feld festgelegt werden welche Information von welcher Seite geladen werden soll.&#10;&#10;Die erste Suche wird immer auf  MusicBrainz durchgeführt. Sollte der allmusic link auf der MusicBrainz Seite fehlen, können keine Informationen von allmusic geladen werden. (diese fehlenden links können sehr leicht nachgetragen werden).</description>
    <description lang="el">Αυτό το scraper συλλέγει πληροφορίες από τις ακόλουθες υποστηριζόμενες ιστοσελίδες: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm και allmusic.com, ενώ λαμβάνει εικόνες από τα: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm και allmusic.com. Μπορεί να οριστεί πεδίο ανά πεδίο αναλόγως των πληροφοριών που επιθυμείτε από την εκάστοτε ιστοσελίδα.&#10;&#10;Η αρχική αναζήτηση γίνεται πάντα στο MusicBrainz. Σε περίπτωση που δεν έχουν προστεθεί σύνδεσμοι για το allmusic στο MusicBrainz, δε θα μπορούν να ληφθούν πεδία από το allmusic.com (ωστόσο είναι πολύ εύκολο να προστεθούν αυτοί οι ελλιπείς σύνδεσμοι).</description>
    <description lang="en">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic link is not added on the MusicBrainz site fields from allmusic.com cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="es">Este scraper recopila información de las siguientes webs: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm y allmusic.com, mientras obtiene las imágenes de fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm y allmusic.com. Permite especificar de qué web se quiere obtener la información específica. ⏎ ⏎ La búsqueda inicial se realiza siempre en MusicBrainz. En caso de que los enlaces a allmusic no estén añadidos en la web de MusicBrainz, no se podrán obtener los campos de información de este sitio (aunque es muy fácil añadir esos enlaces que faltan).</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">Este scraper recopila información de las siguientes webs: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm y allmusic.com, mientras que obtiene las imágenes de fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm y allmusic.com. Permite especificar de qué web se quiere obtener la información específica. ⏎ ⏎ La búsqueda inicial se realiza siempre en MusicBrainz. En caso de que los enlaces a allmusic no estén añadidos en la web de MusicBrainz, no se podrán obtener los campos de información de este sitio (aunque es muy fácil añadir esos enlaces que faltan).</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">Este scraper obtiene información de los siguientes sitios soportados: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm y allmusic.com, mientras obtiene artwork de: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm y allmusic.com. Puede ser configurado campo por campo de que sitio quieres esa información específica.⏎ ⏎ La búsqueda inicial siempre es hecha en MusicBrainz. En el caso en que los enlaces de allmusic no son agregados en el sitio de  MusicBrainz, campos de allmusic.com no pueden ser obtenidos. (De cualquier manera es muy fácil agregar esos enlaces no encontrados).</description>
    <description lang="fi">Tämä tiedonhakija käyttää tietolähteinään seuraavia sivustoja: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com. Kuvat ja grafiikat haetaan seuraavilta sivustoilta: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. Voit määrittää tarkasti, miltä sivustoilta mitäkin tietoa haetaan.&#10;&#10;Ensimmäinen haku tehdään aina lähteestä MusicBrainz. Mikäli allmusic-linkkiä ei ole lisätty MusicBrainz-sivustolle allmusic.com-osoitteessa, haku ei onnistu (mutta puuttuvien linkkien lisääminen on helppoa).</description>
    <description lang="fr">Ce collecteur répertorie les informations des sites suivants : TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, Last.fm et allmusic.com tout en assemblant les illustrations depuis : fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm et allmusic.com. Vous pouvez définir la source d'information pour chaque champ.&#10;&#10;La recherche initiale est toujours faite à partir de MusicBrainz. xxxxxxxx (en attente du retour de l'équipe xbmc) xxxxxxxxxxx</description>
    <description lang="gl">Este scraper recolle información dos seguintes sitios:&#10;TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm e allmusic.com, mentres que, obtén as imaxes de: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm e allmusic.com. Pode definir en cada campo o sitio de onde quere obter a información.&#10;&#10;A busca inicial é feita sempre no MusicBrainz, no caso de que a ligazón a allmusic non se teña engadido nos campos do sítio MusicBrainz dende allmusic.com, non se poderán obter (aínda que, é moi doado engadir as ligazóns que faltan).</description>
    <description lang="he">סקרייפר זה אוסף מידע מהתארים הנתמכים הבאים: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, בעוד שמשיכת גרפיקה נעשית דרך: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. יש אפשרות להגדיר את זאת שדה אחר שדה מאיזה אתר ברצונך למשוך את המידע הספציפי.⏎ ⏎ החיפוש הפנימי נעשה תמיד דרך MusicBrainz. במקרה שקישור allmusic לא התווסף באתר MusicBrainz, השדות מאת allmusic.com אינן יכולות להימשך (למרות שזה מאוד קל להוסיף את הקישורים הריקים).</description>
    <description lang="hu">Ez a leolvasó a következő weboldalakról gyűjti be az adatokat:  TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm és allmusic.com, míg képeket a következő oldalakról gyűjt: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm és allmusic.com. Egyenként beállítható, hogy az adott mezőt melyik weboldalról töltse fel⏎ ⏎ A kiinduló keresés mindig a MusicBrainz. Amennyiben az allmusic utalás nincs hozzáadva MusicBrainz oldalhoz, a mezők nem tölthetők le az allmusic.com oldalról (a hiányzó utalások hozzáadása azonban nagyon egyszerű).</description>
    <description lang="it">Lo scraper colleziona informazioni da questi siti supportati: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, e allmusic.com, mentre ottiene le grafiche da: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm e allmusic.com. Può essere impostato campo per campo da quale sito vuoi la specifica informazione.&#10;&#10;La ricerca iniziale è sempre fatta su MusicBrainz. Nel caso che il link allmusic non è stato aggiunto al campo del sito MusicBrainz da allmusic.com; non possono essere ottenute (è comunque veramente facile aggiungere questi link mancanti).</description>
    <description lang="ja">このスクレーパーは、以下のサイトから情報を取得します：TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com。アートワークは以下のサイトから取得します：fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm, allmusic.com。各フィールドごとに、どの情報をどのサイトから取得するか、個別に指定することもできます。&#10;&#10;最初は MusicBrainz を使って検索が行われます。MusicBrainz サイトに allmusic のリンクが追加されていない場合は、allmusic.com からのフィールドは取得できません (リンクを追加するのは簡単ですが)。</description>
    <description lang="ko">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic link is not added on the MusicBrainz site fields from allmusic.com cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="lt">Šis Scrapers renka informaciją iš šių palaikomų svetainių: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, ir allmusic.com, ir atsiunčia meno kūrinius iš: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm ir allmusic.com. Jis gali būti nustatyti lauko srityje, kurioje svetainėje norite, kad konkrečiu atveju pradinė informacijos pradinis paieška visada bus atlikta remiantis MusicBrainz. Allmusic nuoroda įdėta į MusicBrainz vietoje laukų allmusic.com negali būti (nors tas trūkstamas grandis labai lengva įtraukti).</description>
    <description lang="mk">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic link is not added on the MusicBrainz site fields from allmusic.com cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="nl">Deze scraper verzamelt informatie van de volgende ondersteunde websites: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, en allmusic.com en tevens pakt hij afbeeldingen van fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm en allmusic.com. Het is mogelijk om per veld aan te geven van welke website je de specifieke informatie wil halen. De initiële zoekopdracht wordt altijd uitgevoerd op MusicBrainz. Wanneer de allmusic link niet is toegevoegd in de juiste velden op de MusicBrainz website kan de informatie van allmusic.com niet worden opgehaald. (Het is erg makkelijk om deze ontbrekende links toe te voegen.)</description>
    <description lang="pl">Ten scraper zbiera informacje z następujących stron: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, a grafiki pobiera z: </description>
    <description lang="pt">Este scraper recolhe informações dos seguintes sítios:&#10;TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm e allmusic.com, enquanto obtém artwork de: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm e allmusic.com. Pode definir em cada campo o sítio de onde quer obter as informações.⏎ ⏎ A pesquisa inicial é sempre feita no MusicBrainz. Caso uma ligação allmusic não tenha sido adicionada no sítio MusicBrainz, os campos do allmusic.com não serão obtidos (no entanto, é muito fácil adicionar os links em falta).</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Este scraper coleta informações nos seguintes sites:&#10;MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com e amazon.de, enquanto pega os artwork de: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. O Mesmo pode ser configurara campo a campo em que site você quer obter informações específicas. A procura inicial é sempre feita no MusicBrainz. No caso allmusic e/ou amazon.de não terem sido adicionados no site MusicBrainz, campos de allmusic.com e/ou amazona.de não serão buscados (embora seja muito fácil adicionar os links faltantes). </description>
    <description lang="ro">Acest scraper colectează informații de la următoarele site-uri suportate: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, și allmusic.com, și opere de artă de la: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm și allmusic.com. Poate fi setat câmp cu câmp de pe care site-ul doriți informații specifice ⏎ ⏎ căutarea inițială se face întotdeauna face pe MusicBrainz.. În cazul în care link-ul Allmusic nu este adăugat la MusicBrainz, allmusic.com nu poate fi folosit (însă este relativ ușor să adăugați aceste link-uri lipsă).</description>
    <description lang="ru">Этот скрапер собирает информацию со следующих сайтов: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm и allmusic.com, при этом получая обложки с: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm и allmusic.com. Каждое поле может быть настроено для получения определенной информации с желаемого вами сайта.⏎ ⏎ Первичный поиск всегда производится на MusicBrainz. Если линк для allmusic не добавлен на сайте MusicBrainz, то поля с allmusic.com не могут быть заполнены (добавить отсутствующие ссылки очень легко).</description>
    <description lang="sk">Tento zdroj získavania dát zbiera infomácie z nasledujúcich podporovaných stránok: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm a allmusic.com. Grafiku získava zo stránok: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm a allmusic.com. Je možné podrobne nastaviť, z ktorej stránky chcete získať konkrétne informácie.&#10;&#10;Počiatočné hľadanie je vždy na stránke MusicBrainz. V prípade, že odkaz pre allmusic nie je pridaný na stránku MusicBrainz, nie je možné získať údaje zo stránky allmusic.com (je ale veľmi jednoduché tieto chýbajúce odkazy pridať).</description>
    <description lang="sl">Ta ponudnik združuje informacije s sledečih strani: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm in allmusic.com; grafike prenaša z: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm in allmusic.com. Vsako informacijo lahko prenesete z različne strani.&#10;&#10;Začeno iskanje je vedn na MusicBrainz. V primeru, da na MusicBrainz ni povezave do allmusic.com, informacij od tam ne morete prenesti (a to težavo hitro lahko odpravite).</description>
    <description lang="sv">Denna skrapa samlar information från följande sajter: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm och allmusic.com, medans den samlar konstverk från: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm och allmusic.com. Du kan ange fält för fält från vilken sajt du vill ha den specifika inforamtionen från. Den initiala sökningen är alltid gjord på MusicBrainz. Om inte allmusic.com länken läggs till på MusicBrainz sajten, kan inte fält från allmusic.com hämtas (väldigt enkelt att lägga till dom saknade länkarna dock).</description>
    <description lang="zh">本刮削器支持从以下网站获取信息：TheAudioDb.com、MusicBrainz、last.fm和allmusic.com，并从以下网站获取艺术图片：fanart.tv、htbackdrops.com、last.fm和allmusic.com。你可以指定每一项内容的来源网站。&#10;&#10;初始结果总是先从MusicBrainz获取，如果MusicBrainz网站未加入到allmusic的外部链接，则无法获取allmusic.com的信息（当然你能很容易地加入缺失的链接）。</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="metadata.common.allmusic.com"
       name="AllMusic"
        version="2.6.0"
       provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.library"
             library="allmusic.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <minversion>20000</minversion>
    <summary lang="bg">Библиотека за сваляне на музикална инф. от AllMusic</summary>
    <summary lang="en">AllMusic Music Scraper Library</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Musik-Scraper für AllMusic.com</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Scraper de música de AllMusic</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">AllMusic musiikkitietojen lataajan kirjasto</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Scraper AllMusic pour la musique</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">AllMusic zenei adat leolvasó</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">AllMusic-scraperfuncties</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Scraper muzyki AllMusic</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Scraper de música AllMusic</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Bibliotecă catalog de muzică AllMusic</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Музыкальная Информация AllMusic</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Skrapa för AllMusic.com</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">AllMusic音乐刮削器代码库</summary>
    <description lang="bg">Извлича инф. за музикални файлове от www.allmusic.com</description>
    <description lang="en">Download Music information from www.allmusic.com</description>
    <description lang="de">Downloade Musik Informationen von www.allmusic.com</description>
    <description lang="es">Descarga información musical de www.allmusic.com</description>
    <description lang="fi">Lataa musiikkitietoja osoitteesta www.allmusic.com</description>
    <description lang="fr">Télécharger les infos musicales depuis www.allmusic.com</description>
    <description lang="hu">Zene információk letöltése a www.allmusic.com webhelyről</description>
    <description lang="nl">Muziekinformatie ophalen van www.allmusic.com</description>
    <description lang="pl">Pobieraj informacje o muzyce z www.allmusic.com</description>
    <description lang="pt">Descarregar informação de música de www.allmusic.com</description>
    <description lang="ro">Descărcați informații muzică de pe www.allmusic.com</description>
    <description lang="ru">Загружать информацию о Музыке с www.allmusic.com</description>
    <description lang="se">Ladda ner musikinformation från www.allmusic.com</description>
    <description lang="zh">从www.allmusic.com下载音乐信息</description>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="metadata.common.amazon.de"
       name="Amazon.de"
       version="1.0.0"
       provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.library"
             library="amazonde.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <minversion>20000</minversion>
    <summary lang="en">amazon.de Scraper Library</summary>
    <description lang="en">Download Music information from amazon.de</description>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="metadata.common.fanart.tv"
       name="fanart.tv"
       version="2.1.2"
       provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.library"
             library="fanarttv.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <minversion>20000</minversion>
    <summary lang="bg">Библиотека за сваляне на инф. от fanart.tv</summary>
    <summary lang="en">fanart.tv Scraper Library</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Scraper für Hintergründe von fanart.tv</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Scraper de fanart.tv</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">fanart.tv taustakuvalataajan kirjasto</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Scraper fanart.tv</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">fanart.tv leolvasó-könyvtár</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">fanart.tv-scraperfuncties</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Scraper biblioteki fanart.tv</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Biblioteca de fundos fanart.tv</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Обработчик Фоновых изображений с fanart.tv</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Skrapa för fanart.tv</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">fanart.tv刮削器代码库</summary>
    <description lang="bg">Сваля декорации от www.fanart.tv.com</description>
    <description lang="en">Download backdrops from www.fanart.tv.com</description>
    <description lang="de">Downloade Hintergründe von www.fanart.tv.com</description>
    <description lang="es">Descarga fanart y fotos de artistas de www.fanart.tv.com</description>
    <description lang="fi">Lataa taustakuvia osoitteesta www.fanart.tv.com</description>
    <description lang="fr">Télécharge les backdrops depuis www.htbackgrops.com</description>
    <description lang="hu">Fanartképek letöltése www.fanart.tv.com webhelyről</description>
    <description lang="nl">Achtergronden ophalen van www.fanart.tv.com</description>
    <description lang="pl">Pobieraj tła z www.fanart.tv.com</description>
    <description lang="pt">Descarregar fundos de www.fanart.tv.com</description>
    <description lang="ru">Загружать фоновые изображения с www.fanart.tv.com</description>
    <description lang="se">Ladda ner bakgrundsbilder från www.fanart.tv.com</description>
    <description lang="zh">从www.fanart.tv.com下载背景图</description>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="metadata.common.hdtrailers.net"
       name="HD-Trailers common scraper functions"
       version="1.0.8"
       provider-name="Bence Nádas (olympia)">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.library"
             library="hdtrailers.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">HD-Trailers.net Scraper Library</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Scraper für Trailer von HD-Trailers.net</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Scraper de Trailers de HD-Trailers.net</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Scraper HD-Trailers.net pour les bande-annonces</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">HD-Trailers.net leolvasó-könyvtár</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">HD-Trailers.net Scraper Collectie</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Scraper zwiastunów HD-Trailers.net</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Scraper de trailers de HD-Trailers.net</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Обработчик для трейлеров с HD-Trailers.net</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">HD-Trailers.net刮削器代码库</summary>
    <description lang="en">Download Movie Trailers from www.hd-trailers.net</description>
    <description lang="de">Downloade Trailer von www.hd-trailers.net</description>
    <description lang="es">Descarga trailers de www.hd-trailers.net</description>
    <description lang="fr">Télécharge les bande-annonces de films depuis www.hd-trailers.net</description>
    <description lang="hu">Filmelőzetesek letöltése a www.hd-trailers.net-ről</description>
    <description lang="nl">Download trailers van www.hd-trailers.net</description>
    <description lang="pl">Pobieraj zwiastuny filmowe z www.hd-trailers.net</description>
    <description lang="pt">Descarregar trailers de www.hd-trailers.net</description>
    <description lang="ru">Загружать трейлеры с www.hd-trailers.net</description>
    <description lang="zh">从www.hd-trailers.net下载电影预告片</description>
    <minversion>20000</minversion>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="metadata.common.htbackdrops.com"
       name="HTBackdrops"
       version="1.2.0"
       provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.library"
             library="htbackdrops.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <minversion>20000</minversion>
    <summary lang="bg">Библиотека за сваляне на инф. от HTBackdrops</summary>
    <summary lang="en">HTBackdrops Scraper Library</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Scraper für Hintergründe von HTBackdrops</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Scraper de HTBackdrops</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">HTBackdrops taustakuvalataajan kirjasto</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Scraper HTBackdrops</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">HTBackdrops leolvasó-könyvtár</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">HTBackdrops-scraperfuncties</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Scraper biblioteki HTBackdrops</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Biblioteca de fundos HTBackdrops</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Обработчик Фоновых изображений с HTBackdrops</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Skrapa för HTBackdrops</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">HTBackdrops刮削器代码库</summary>
    <description lang="bg">Сваля декорации от www.htbackdrops.com</description>
    <description lang="en">Download backdrops from www.htbackdrops.com</description>
    <description lang="de">Downloade Hintergründe von www.htbackdrops.com</description>
    <description lang="es">Descarga fanart y fotos de artistas de www.htbackdrops.com</description>
    <description lang="fi">Lataa taustakuvia osoitteesta www.htbackdrops.com</description>
    <description lang="fr">Télécharge les backdrops depuis www.htbackgrops.com</description>
    <description lang="hu">Fanartképek letöltése www.htbackdrops.com webhelyről</description>
    <description lang="nl">Achtergronden ophalen van www.htbackdrops.com</description>
    <description lang="pl">Pobieraj tła z www.htbackdrops.com</description>
    <description lang="pt">Descarregar fundos de www.htbackdrops.com</description>
    <description lang="ru">Загружать фоновые изображения с www.htbackdrops.com</description>
    <description lang="se">Ladda ner bakgrundsbilder från www.htbackdrops.com</description>
    <description lang="zh">从www.htbackdrops.com下载背景图</description>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="metadata.common.imdb.com"
       name="IMDB Scraper Library"
       version="2.7.6"
       provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.library"
             library="imdb.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <minversion>20000</minversion>
    <summary lang="bg">Библиотека за сваляне на инф. от IMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="en">IMDB Scraper Library</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">IMDB elokuvatietojen lataaja</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">IMDB leolvasó-könyvtár</summary>
    <summary lang="kr">IMDB 스크래퍼 라이브러리</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">IMDB Scraper Bibliotheek</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Scraper IMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Scraper de filmes IMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Skrapa för IMDB</summary>
    <description lang="bg">Сваля информация за филми от www.imdb.com</description>
    <description lang="en">Download Movie information from www.imdb.com</description>
    <description lang="fi">Lataa elokuvatietoja osoitteesta www.imdb.com</description>
    <description lang="hu">Film információk letöltése a www.imdb.com webhelyről</description>
    <description lang="kr">www.imdb.com 에서 영화 정보 다운로드</description>
    <description lang="nl">Download film informatie van www.imdb.com</description>
    <description lang="pl">Pobieraj informacje o filmach z www.imdb.com</description>
    <description lang="pt">Descarregar informação de filmes de www.imdb.com</description>
    <description lang="se">Ladda ner filminformation från www.imdb.com</description>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="metadata.common.last.fm"
       name="Last.FM"
       version="1.6.0"
       provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.library"
             library="lastfm.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <minversion>20000</minversion>
    <summary lang="bg">Библиотека за сваляне на инф. от LastFM</summary>
    <summary lang="en">LastFM Scraper Library</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Musik-Scraper für LastFM</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Scraper de música de LastFM</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">LastFM musiikkitietojen lataaja</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Scraper LastFM</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">LastFM leolvasó-könyvtár</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">LastFM-scraperfuncties</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Scraper biblioteki LastFM</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Scraper de música LastFM</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Обработчик для LastFM</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Skrapebibliotek för LastFM</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">LastFM刮削器代码库</summary>
    <description lang="bg">Извлича инф. за музикални файлове от www.last.fm</description>
    <description lang="en">Download Music information from www.last.fm</description>
    <description lang="de">Downloade Musik informationen von www.last.fm</description>
    <description lang="es">Descargar información musical de www.last.fm</description>
    <description lang="fi">Lataa musiikkitietoja osoitteesta www.last.fm</description>
    <description lang="fr">Télécharge les infos musicales depuis www.last.fm</description>
    <description lang="hu">Zene információk letöltése a www.last.fm webhelyről</description>
    <description lang="nl">Muziekinfo ophalen van LastFM</description>
    <description lang="pl">Pobieraj informacje o muzyce z www.last.fm</description>
    <description lang="pt">Descarregar informação de música de www.last.fm</description>
    <description lang="ru">Загружать информацию о Музыке с www.last.fm</description>
    <description lang="se">Ladda ner musikinformation från www.last.fm</description>
    <description lang="zh">从www.last.fm下载音乐信息</description>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="metadata.common.musicbrainz.org"
       name="musicbrainz"
        version="1.3.0"
       provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.library"
             library="musicbrainz.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <minversion>20000</minversion>
    <summary lang="bg">Библиотека за сваляне на музикална инф. от MusicBrainz</summary>
    <summary lang="en">MusicBrainz Music Scraper Library</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Musik-Scraper für musicbrainz.org</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Scraper de música de MusicBrainz</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">MusicBrainz musiikkitietojen lataajan kirjasto</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Scraper MusicBrainz pour la musique</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">MusicBrainz zenei adat leolvasó</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">MusicBrainz-scraperfuncties</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Scraper muzyki MusicBrainz</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Scraper de música MusicBrainz</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Bibliotecă catalog de muzică MusicBrainz</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Музыкальная Информация MusicBrainz</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Skrapa för musicbrainz.org</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">MusicBrainz音乐刮削器代码库</summary>
    <description lang="bg">Извлича инф. за музикални файлове от www.musicbrainz.org</description>
    <description lang="en">Download Music information from www.musicbrainz.org</description>
    <description lang="de">Downloade Musik Informationen von www.musicbrainz.org</description>
    <description lang="es">Descarga información musical de www.musicbrainz.org</description>
    <description lang="fi">Lataa musiikkitietoja osoitteesta www.musicbrainz.org</description>
    <description lang="fr">Télécharger les infos musicales depuis www.musicbrainz.org</description>
    <description lang="hu">Zene információk letöltése a www.musicbrainz.org webhelyről</description>
    <description lang="nl">Muziekinformatie ophalen van www.musicbrainz.org</description>
    <description lang="pl">Pobieraj informacje o muzyce z www.musicbrainz.org</description>
    <description lang="pt">Descarregar informação de música de www.musicbrainz.org</description>
    <description lang="ro">Descărcați informații muzică de pe www.musicbrainz.org</description>
    <description lang="ru">Загружать информацию о Музыке с www.musicbrainz.org</description>
    <description lang="se">Ladda ner musikinformation från www.musicbrainz.org</description>
    <description lang="zh">从www.musicbrainz.org下载音乐信息</description>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="metadata.common.theaudiodb.com"
       name="TheAudioDb Common Scraper Functions"
       version="1.5.0"
       provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.library"
             library="tadb.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <minversion>20000</minversion>
    <summary lang="bg">Библиотека за сваляне на музикална инф. от TheAudioDb</summary>
    <summary lang="en">TheAudioDb Music Scraper Library</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Musik-Scraper für TheAudioDb.org</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Scraper de música de TheAudioDb</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">TheAudioDb musiikkitietojen lataajan kirjasto</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Scraper TheAudioDb pour la musique</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">TheAudioDb zenei adat leolvasó</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">TheAudioDb-scraperfuncties</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Scraper muzyki TheAudioDb</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Scraper de música TheAudioDb</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Bibliotecă catalog de muzică TheAudioDb</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Музыкальная Информация TheAudioDb</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Skrapa för TheAudioDb.org</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">TheAudioDb音乐刮削器代码库</summary>
    <description lang="bg">Извлича инф. за музикални файлове от www.theaudiodb.com</description>
    <description lang="en">Download Music information from www.theaudiodb.com</description>
    <description lang="de">Downloade Musik Informationen von www.theaudiodb.com</description>
    <description lang="es">Descarga información musical de www.theaudiodb.com</description>
    <description lang="fi">Lataa musiikkitietoja osoitteesta www.theaudiodb.com</description>
    <description lang="fr">Télécharger les infos musicales depuis www.theaudiodb.com</description>
    <description lang="hu">Zene információk letöltése a www.theaudiodb.com webhelyről</description>
    <description lang="nl">Muziekinformatie ophalen van www.theaudiodb.com</description>
    <description lang="pl">Pobieraj informacje o muzyce z www.theaudiodb.com</description>
    <description lang="pt">Descarregar informação de música de www.theaudiodb.com</description>
    <description lang="ro">Descărcați informații muzică de pe www.theaudiodb.com</description>
    <description lang="ru">Загружать информацию о Музыке с www.theaudiodb.com</description>
    <description lang="se">Ladda ner musikinformation från www.theaudiodb.com</description>
    <description lang="zh">从www.theaudiodb.com下载音乐信息</description>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="metadata.common.themoviedb.org"
       name="The Movie Database Scraper Library"
       version="2.9.3"
       provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.library"
             library="tmdb.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <minversion>20000</minversion>
    <summary lang="bg">Библиотека за сваляне на инф. от TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="en">TMDb Scraper Library</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Scraper de peliculas de TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">TMDb elokuvatietojen lataajan kirjasto</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Scraper TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">TMDb leolvasó-könyvtár</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">TMDb-scraperfuncties</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Scraper biblioteki TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Scraper de filmes TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Bibliotecă catalog TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Обработчик для TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Skrapebibliotek för TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">TMDb刮削器代码库</summary>
    <description lang="bg">Сваля миниатюри и fanarts от www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="en">Download thumbs and fanarts from www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="es">Descarga posters y fanart de www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="fi">Lataa pienoiskuvia ja fanitaidetta www.themoviedb.org -sivustolta</description>
    <description lang="fr">Télécharge vignettes et backdrops depuis www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="hu">Bélyeg- és fanartképek letöltése a www.themoviedb.org webhelyről</description>
    <description lang="nl">Miniaturen en fanart ophalen van www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="pl">Pobieraj ikony i fanarty z www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="pt">Descarregar informação de filmes de www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="ro">Descărcați miniaturi și imagini realizate de fani de pe www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="ru">Загружать миниатюры и фанарт с www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="se">Ladda ner miniatyrer och fanart från www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="zh">从www.themoviedb.org下载海报和同人画</description>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="metadata.musicvideos.last.fm"
       name="Last.fm for Music Videos"
       version="1.0.0"
       provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.last.fm" version="1.3.2"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.fanart.tv" version="1.0.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.musicvideos"
             language="en"
             library="lastfmmusicvideos.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="bg">Сваля инф. за музикални клипове от Last.fm</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Last.fm Music Video Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">Last.fm musiikkivideotietojen lataaja</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Last.fm videóklip leolvasó</summary>
    <summary lang="kr">야후! 뮤직 비디오 스크래퍼</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Scraper teledysków Last.fm</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Scraper de música Last.fm</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Skrapa för Last.fm musik</summary>
    <description lang="bg">Сваля информация за музикални клипове</description>
    <description lang="en">Download Music Video information</description>
    <description lang="fi">Lataa musiikkivideoiden tiedot</description>
    <description lang="hu">Videóklip információk letöltése a Last.fm webhelyről</description>
    <description lang="kr">뮤직 비디오 정보 다운로드</description>
    <description lang="pl">Pobieraj informacje o teledyskach z last.fm</description>
    <description lang="pt">Descarregar informação de filmes de last.fm</description>
    <description lang="se">Ladda ner musikvideoinformation från last.fm</description>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="metadata.musicvideos.theaudiodb.com"
       name="TheAudioDb.com for Music Videos"
       version="1.0.4"
       provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.fanart.tv" version="2.1.2"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.musicvideos"
             language="en"
             library="tadb.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af">theaudiodb.com Musiek Video Skraper</summary>
    <summary lang="be">theaudiodb.com Music Video Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="bg">Сваля инф. за музикални клипове от theaudiodb.com</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">Zdroj dat o hudebních videích theaudiodb.com</summary>
    <summary lang="da">theaudiodb.com Musikvideo-scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="de">theaudiodb.com Musikvideo-Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Scraper Μουσικών Βίντεο του theaudiodb.com</summary>
    <summary lang="en">theaudiodb.com Music Video Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Buscador de videoclips de theaudiodb.com</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Scraper de Videos de Música de TheAudioDb.com</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">theaudiodb.com musiikkivideotietojen lataaja</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">theaudiodb.com Scraper Clip Vidéo</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">Scraper de vídeo e música de theaudiodb.com</summary>
    <summary lang="he">theaudiodb.com סקרייפר וידאו קליפ</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">theaudiodb.com videóklip leolvasó</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Lo scraper di video musicali theaudiodb.com</summary>
    <summary lang="ja">theaudiodb.com 音楽ビデオスクレーパー</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">야후! 뮤직 비디오 스크래퍼</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">theaudiodb.com vaizdo klipų Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="mk">theaudiodb.com Music Video Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">theaudiodb.com Muziek Video Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="no">theaudiodb.com Skraper for musikkvideo</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Scraper teledysków theaudiodb.com</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Scraper de música theaudiodb.com</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Scraper de concertos theaudiodb.com</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Informaţii videoclipuri de la theaudiodb.com </summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Скрапер музыки и видео theaudiodb.com</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Skrapa för theaudiodb.com musik</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">Zdroj získavania dát o hudobných videách zo stránky theaudiodb.com</summary>
    <summary lang="sl">Ponudnik informacij o videospotih theaudiodb.com</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">theaudiodb.com musikvideoskrapa</summary>
    <summary lang="th">ตัวดึงข้อมูลวิดีโอเพลง theaudiodb.com</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">theaudiodb.com音乐电视刮削器</summary>
    <description lang="af">Laai Musiek Video informasie af</description>
    <description lang="am">የሙዚቃ ቪዲዮ መረጃ ማውረጃ</description>
    <description lang="be">Download Music Video information</description>
    <description lang="bg">Сваля информация за музикални клипове</description>
    <description lang="ca">Baixa informació de videos musicals</description>
    <description lang="cs">Stáhnout informace o hudebním videu</description>
    <description lang="da">Hent Musikvideo-information</description>
    <description lang="de">Musik Video Information herunterladen</description>
    <description lang="el">Λήψη πληροφοριών Μουσικών Βίντεο</description>
    <description lang="en">Download Music Video information</description>
    <description lang="es">Descarga información del videoclip</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">Descarga información del Video Clip</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">Descarga Información de Vídeos de Músca</description>
    <description lang="fi">Lataa musiikkivideoiden tiedot</description>
    <description lang="fr">Télécharger les informations des clips vidéos</description>
    <description lang="gl">Descargar a información do vídeo e música</description>
    <description lang="he">הורד מידע וידאו קליפ</description>
    <description lang="hu">Videóklip információk letöltése a theaudiodb.com webhelyről</description>
    <description lang="it">Scarica informazioni Video Musicale</description>
    <description lang="ja">音楽ビデオの情報をダウンロード</description>
    <description lang="ko">뮤직 비디오 정보 다운로드</description>
    <description lang="lt">Atsisiusti vaizdo klipų informaciją</description>
    <description lang="mk">Превземи информации за музичко видео</description>
    <description lang="nl">Muziek Video informatie downloaden</description>
    <description lang="no">Last ned musikkvideoinformasjon</description>
    <description lang="pl">Pobieraj informacje o teledyskach z theaudiodb.com</description>
    <description lang="pt">Descarregar informação de filmes de theaudiodb.com</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Download de informação de Concertos</description>
    <description lang="ro">Descarcă informaţii videoclipuri</description>
    <description lang="ru">Загружать сведения о видеоклипах</description>
    <description lang="se">Ladda ner musikvideoinformation från theaudiodb.com</description>
    <description lang="sk">Prevziať informácie o hudobnom videu</description>
    <description lang="sl">Prenesite informacije o videospotih</description>
    <description lang="sv">Ladda ner musikvideoinformation</description>
    <description lang="th">ดาวน์โหลดข้อมูลวิดีโอเพลง</description>
    <description lang="zh">从theaudiodb.com下载音乐电视资料</description>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="metadata.themoviedb.org"
       name="The Movie Database"
       version="3.7.2"
       provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.themoviedb.org" version="2.8.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.hdtrailers.net" version="1.0.7"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.imdb.com" version="2.6.0"/>
    <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" version="2.9.1" optional="true"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.movies"
             language="en"
             library="tmdb.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af">TMDB Fliek Skraper</summary>
    <summary lang="be">TMDB Movie Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="bg">Сваля инф. за филми от TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">Arreplegador de pel·lícules TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">Zdroj zisku dat k filmům TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="da">TMDB Scraper til Film</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Film Scraper für TheMovieDB</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Scraper Ταινιών του TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="en">TMDB Movie Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Scraper de películas de TheMovieDB</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Scraper de Películas de TheMovieDB</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Scraper de Películas TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="et">TMDB Filmi kaabits</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">TMDB elokuvatietojen lataaja</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Collecteur de Films TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">Scraper de Filme de TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="he">TMDB סקרייפר סרטים</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">TMDB filmadat leolvasó</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Ricercatore per TMDB Movie</summary>
    <summary lang="ja">TMDB映画のスクレーパー</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">TMDB 영화 자료수집기</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">TMDB Filmų Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="mk">TMDB инфо за филмови</summary>
    <summary lang="ml">മൂവി ഡി ബി, വിവരശേഖരം</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">TMDb-filmscraper</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Scraper filmowy TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Scraper de filmes TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Scraper de Filmes TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Scraper de filme TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Инфоресурс на базе TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Skrapa för TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">TheMovieDB filmový sťahovač</summary>
    <summary lang="sl">Ponudnik informacij o filmih TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">TMDB Filmskrapa</summary>
    <summary lang="th">ตัวรับข้อมูลภาพยนต์ TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">TMDB电影刮削器</summary>
    <description lang="af">themoviedb.org is 'n verniet en oop fliek databasis. Dit is totaal gebruiker gedryf deur mense soos jy. TMDB word huidiglik deur miljoene mense elke maand gebruik, en met hulle kragtige API word dit ook deur baie gewilde media sentrums soos XBMC gebruik om Fliek Metadata, Plakkate en Ondersteunerkuns te onttrek om die gebruiker se ondervinding te verryk.</description>
    <description lang="be">themoviedb.org is a free and open movie database. It's completely user driven by people like you. TMDb is currently used by millions of people every month and with their powerful API, it is also used by many popular media centers like XBMC to retrieve Movie Metadata, Posters and Fanart to enrich the user's experience.</description>
    <description lang="bg">themoviedb.org е безплатна и отворена база от данни за филми. Задвижва се изцяло от потребителите си - хора като вас. Милиони хора по света всеки месец ползват TMDb, благодарение на многофункционалното API. Едновременно с това е и източник на информация за медийни центрове, като XBMC, които извличат метаинформация за филми, постери и Fanart.</description>
    <description lang="ca">themoviedb.org és una base de dades oberta i lliure. Es manté completament per usuaris, per gent com tu. TMDb s'utilitza actualment per milions de persones cada mes i amb la seva potent API també és utilitzada per molts centre media populas com l'XBMC per obtenir les meta-dades de pel·lícules, pósters i fanart per enriquir l'experiència d'usuari.</description>
    <description lang="cs">themoviedb.org je otevřená a svobodná databáze filmů. Je řízena uživateli, tedy lidmi jako vy. TMDB je každý měsíc používána milióny lidí a se svým výborným API je také používano mnoha populárními mediálními centry jako je XBMC, k získávání metadat, plagátů a fanartu filmů pro obohacení uživatelského zážitku.</description>
    <description lang="da">themoviedb.org er en fri og åben filmdatabase. Den er helt og aldeles brugerdrevet af folk som dig. TMDb bruges i dag af millioner af mennesker hver måned, og med deres kraftfulde API er den også brugt af mange populære mediecentre såsom XBMC til at hente metadata, plakater og fankunst til film, for at berige brugerens oplevelse.</description>
    <description lang="de">TheMovieDB.org ist eine freie und offene Filmdatenbank. Sie wird von Benutzern wie Dir betrieben. TheMovieDB wird zur Zeit monatlich von Millionen genutzt. Mit der mächtigen API wird sie auch von vielen Media-Center, wie z.B. XBMC, genutzt um Film Metadaten, Poster und Fanarts zu beziehen, damit der Benutzer sein Media-Center verschönern kann.</description>
    <description lang="el">Το themoviedb.org είναι μία δωρεάν και ανοικτή βάση δεδομένων ταινιών. Διαχειρίζεται πλήρως από ανθρώπους σαν και εσάς. Το TMDb χρησιμοποιείται από εκατομμύρια ανθρώπους κάθε μήνα, και με το πανίσχυρο API τους, χρησιμοποιείται και από πολλά δημοφιλή κέντρα πολυμέσων όπως το XBMC για να λαμβάνουν μετα-δεδομένα Ταινιών, Αφίσες και Fanart για εμπλουτισμό της εμπειρίας του χρήστη.</description>
    <description lang="en">themoviedb.org is a free and open movie database. It's completely user driven by people like you. TMDb is currently used by millions of people every month and with their powerful API, it is also used by many popular media centers like XBMC to retrieve Movie Metadata, Posters and Fanart to enrich the user's experience.</description>
    <description lang="es">themovieDB.org es una base de datos de películas gratuita y abierta. Es una página web que se basa en contenido subido por los usuarios. TMDb es usada diariamente por mucha gente gracias a su API, que es usada por más programas aparte de XBMC para descargar información de películas así como Posters o Fanart (Fondos de escritorio basados en películas usados en distintos skins) para enriquecer la experiencia de usar XBMC.</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">themovieDB.org es una base de datos de películas gratuita y abierta. Está  formada con contenido subido por usuarios como vos. TMDb es actualmente utilizada por millones de personas cada mes y, gracias a su poderosa API, es usada por muchos programas populares como XBMC para descargar Información de Películas, Posters y Fanart para enriquecer la experiencia de usar XBMC.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">themoviedb.org es una base de datos de películas gratis y abierta. Es completamente manejada por usuarios y personas como tu. Actualmente TMDb es usada por millones de personas cada mes, y dado a su poderosa API, es usada también por varios media centers populares como XBMC para obtener Metada de Películas, Posters y Fanarts, enriqueciendo de esta manera la experiencia del usuario.</description>
    <description lang="et">themoviedb.org on tasuta ja vaba juurdepääsuga filmide andmebaas.See on täielikult koostatud sinu sarnaste inimeste poolt. TMDb on hetkel igapäevaselt kasutuses miljonite inimeste poolt ja seda kasutavad paljud populaarsed meediakeskused, nagu ka XBMC, filmiandmete, fännikunsti ja posterite leidmiseks.</description>
    <description lang="fi">themoviedb.org on vapaa ja avoin elokuvatietokanta. Se on täysin käyttäjien ylläpitämä. TMDb:a käyttää miljoonat ihmiset joka kuukausi, sitä käytetään käyttäjäkokemuksen rikastuttamiseen monissa muissakin suosituissa XBMC:n kaltaisissa ohjelmissa lataamalla elokuvien tietoja, julisteita ja fanitaidetta.</description>
    <description lang="fr">themoviedb.org est une base de données gratuite et libre d'accès de films. Elle est totalement gérée par les utilisateurs. TMDb est actuellement utilisée par des millions de personnes chaque mois et, grâce à ses puissantes fonctions et routines, elle est également utilisée par de nombreux Media Centers populaires comme XBMC aux fins de récupération des Métadonnées, Posters et Fanarts des films en vue d'améliorer l'expérience de l'utilisateur.</description>
    <description lang="gl">themoviedb.org é una base de datos sobre filmes libre e aberta, impulsada por xente coma ti. Na actualidade TMDb é usada por millóns de persoas todos os meses, e grazas ó seu potente API, usado por algúns dos centros multimedia máis populares como XBMC para obter a información dos filmes, Posters e Fanart e así mellorar a experiencia do usuario.</description>
    <description lang="he">themoviedb.org is a free and open movie database. It's completely user driven by people like you. TMDb is currently used by millions of people every month and with their powerful API, it is also used by many popular media centers like XBMC to retrieve Movie Metadata, Posters and Fanart to enrich the user's experience.</description>
    <description lang="hu">A themoviedb.org egy ingyenes és nyílt filmadatbázis. Teljes egészében olyan felhasználók töltik fel, mint például Te. A TMDb-t havonta emberek milliói használják és a hatékony API-n keresztül számos népszerű média center is, mint például az XBMC a filmadatok, poszterek, fanartképek letöltésére.</description>
    <description lang="it">themoviedb.org è un database libero e aperto. E' gestito da utenti e persone come te. Viene usato correntemente da millioni di persone ogni mese e con le sue potenti API, è anche utilizzato da molti popolari media centers come XBMC per ottenere Metadati, Posters e Fanart di film per arricchire la loro esperienza utente.</description>
    <description lang="ja">themoviedb.org は自由でオープンな映画データベースです。その運営は、完全にユーザ主導で行われています。TMDb は現在毎月何百万人もの人に利用されているほか、XBMC のようなメディアセンターも、TMDb のパワフルな API を介して映画メタデータ、ポスター、ファンアートを取得し、使い勝手を向上させるなどして使っています。</description>
    <description lang="ko">themoviedb.org 는 전적으로 여러분 같은 이용자가 주도하는 무료 공개 영화 데이터베이스입니다. TMDb 는 현재 매월 수백만의 사람들이 강력한 API와 함께 사용하고 있을 뿐만 아니라 XBMC 같은 많은 미디어 센터가 영화 정보, 포스터, 팬아트를 가져와 풍성한 사용자 경험을 제공하는데 이용되고 있습니다.</description>
    <description lang="lt">themoviedb.org yra nemokama ir atvira Filmų duomenų bazė. Jis remiamas ir skaitinamas tokių pat vartotojų kaip ir jūs. TMDb šiuo metu naudoja milijonai žmonių kiekvieną mėnesį, ir turi galingą API (informacinį centrą), taip pat naudojamas daug populiarių žiniasklaidos centrų. Pavyzdžiui XBMC gauti filmo(-ų) metaduomenis, plakatus ir FanArt siekiant praturtinti vartotojo patirtį.</description>
    <description lang="mk">themoviedb.org is a free and open movie database. It's completely user driven by people like you. TMDb is currently used by millions of people every month and with their powerful API, it is also used by many popular media centers like XBMC to retrieve Movie Metadata, Posters and Fanart to enrich the user's experience.</description>
    <description lang="ml">മൂവി ഡി ബി, എല്ലാവർക്കും കൈവക്കാവുന്ന ഒരു സൗജന്യ വിവരശേഖരമാണ്. ഇതുമൂലം ലോകം മുഴുവനും സിനിമാ പോസ്റ്ററുകൾ എല്ലവരും കാണുന്നു</description>
    <description lang="nl">Themoviedb.org is een vrije en open filmdatabank. Gebruikers zoals jij vormen de motor van deze site. Op dit moment gebruiken elke maand miljoenen mensen TMDb. De krachtige API van de site laat mediacenters zoals XBMC toe om metadata, posters en fanart op te halen en zo de gebruikerservaring te verrijken.</description>
    <description lang="pl">themoviedb.org jest wolną i otwartą filmową bazą danych. Jest zarządzana całkowicie przez osoby takie jak Ty. Obecnie odwiedzają ją miliony osób miesięcznie, a dzięki dostępności API jest używana w wielu media center, takich jak XBMC, do pobierania informacji o filmach, plakatów i fanartów.</description>
    <description lang="pt">O themoviedb.org é uma base de dados de filmes livre e aberta. É actualizado inteiramente por pessoas como você e usado por milhões todos os meses. Com o poderoso motor de busca disponível, também se tornou no favorito para muitos programas de centro de média, como o popular XBMC, para obter informação, posters e fanart que enriquecem a experiência do utilizador.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">O themoviedb.org é um banco de dados aberto e gratuito. É completamente operado por pessoas como você. O TMDb é atualmente usado por milhares de pessoas a cada mês e com sua poderosa API, é usado por muitas centrais de mídia populares como o XBMC para buscar metadados, cartazes e fanart de filmes para enriquecer a experiência do usuário.</description>
    <description lang="ro">themoviedb.org este o bază de date de filme gratuită și deschisă. Este actualizată de oameni ca și tine. TMDb este curent folosită de milioane de oameni în fiecare lună și datorită API-ului puternic, este de asemena folosită de multe centre media populare ca XBMC pentru a obține informații despre filme, afișe și imagini produse de fani (Fanart) care îmbogățesc experiența utilizatorului.</description>
    <description lang="ru">themoviedb.org — это бесплатная и открытая база данных фильмов. Она полностью поддерживается обычными людьми. В данный момент сайт TMDb используют миллионы людей каждый месяц, и благодаря мощному API его могут использовать различные популярные медиацентры, такие как XBMC, чтобы получать метаданные, постеры и фанарт для фильмов с целью красивого оформления интерфейса.</description>
    <description lang="se">themoviedb.org är en fri och öppen filmdatabas. Det drivs helt av människor som dig. TMDb används av miljontals människor varje månad och med deras kraftfulla API, är det också använt av många populära mediacenter som XBMC för att hämta filmmetadata, omslag och fanart för att förgylla användarens upplevelse.</description>
    <description lang="sk">themoviedb.org je voľná a otvorená databáza filmov. Je výlučne vedená užívateľmi ako si ty. TMDb je každý mesiac používaná miliónmi ľudí, a vďaka svojmu výkonnému API je veľmi populárna medzi 'media centrami' ako XBMC pre sťahovanie filmových metadát, plagátov a fanartov pre obohatenie  zážitkov.</description>
    <description lang="sl">themoviedb.org je brezplačna in prosta baza filmov. Je v celoti ustvarjena s strani uporabnikov kot ste vi. TMDB uporablja miljone ljudi in z njihovo močno API, jo lahko uporabljate tudi v multimedijskih centrih kot XBMC, s tem prenesete informacije o filmih, plakate in ozadja ter s tem popestrite uporabniško izkušnjo.</description>
    <description lang="sv">themoviedb.org är en gratis och öppen filmdatabas. Den drivs helt av människor som du. TMDb används för närvarande av miljoner människor varje månad och med deras kraftfulla API används den även av många populära mediacenter som t.ex. XBMC för att hämta metadata om filmer, affischer och fanart för att berika användarens upplevelse.</description>
    <description lang="th">themoviedb.org เป็นฐานข้อมูลภาพยนตร์ที่ฟรีและเปิดกว้าง. มันถูกขับเคลื่อนจากผู้ใช้ โดยคนเช่นคุณ. TMDb ปัจจุบันมีการใช้โดยคนนับล้านในแต่ละเดือน และมีประสิทธิภาพด้วย API ของพวกเขา , มันยังถูกใช้โดยหลายศูนย์สื่อที่นิยมเช่น XBMC เพื่อดึง อธิบายข้อมูลภาพยนตร์, โปสเตอร์และ แฟนอาร์ต เพื่อเพิ่มประสบการณ์ของผู้ใช้</description>
    <description lang="zh">themoviedb.org是一个开放和自由的电影数据库。它完全由象你一样的用户来掌控。TMDb每月为上百万用户提供服务，并通过强大的API界面为许多流行的媒体中心系统如XBMC提供电影资料、封面海报和同人画以丰富用户的体验。</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="metadata.tvdb.com"
       name="The TVDB"
       version="1.4.5"
       provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.tvshows"
             language="multi"
             library="tvdb.xml"
             cachepersistence="00:15"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af">Gaan haal TV vertoning metadata vanaf TheTVDB.com</summary>
    <summary lang="be">Fetch TV show metadata from TheTVDB.com</summary>
    <summary lang="bg">Изтегля информация за ТВ Сериали от TheTVDB.com</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">Získat metadata televizního pořadu z TheTVDB.com</summary>
    <summary lang="da">Hent metadata til TV-serier fra TheTVDB.com</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Scraper für Fernsehserien von TheTVDB.com</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Λήψη μετα-δεδομένων σειρών από το TVDB.com</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Fetch TV show metadata from TheTVDB.com</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Recuperar metadatos de series de TV en TheTVDB.com</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Recuperar metadatos de series de TV en TheTVDB.com</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Obtener metadata de Series desde TheTVDB.com</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">Nouda TV-ohjelmien tietoja TheTVDB.com -sivustolta</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Collecter les métadonnées des séries TV depuis TheTVDB.com</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">Obter os metadatos das series de TV dende TheTVDB.com</summary>
    <summary lang="he">הבא מידע </summary>
    <summary lang="hu">TV műsor információk a TheTVDB.com-ról</summary>
    <summary lang="is">Sækja Sjónvarpsþátta lýsigögn frá TheTVDB.com</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Scarica informazioni programma TV da TheTVDB.com</summary>
    <summary lang="ja">TheTVDB.com からTV番組メタデータを取得</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">TheTVDB.com 에서 TV 쇼 정보 가져오기</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">Parsiųsti TV šou (serialo) metaduomenis iš TheTVDB.com</summary>
    <summary lang="mk">Превземи ТВ шоу метаподаток од TVDB.com</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Seriemetadata ophalen van TheTVDB.com</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Pobieraj dane o serialach TV z TheTVDB.com</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Obtenha dados para séries TV de TVDB.com</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Obtenha dados dos seriados do TheTVDB.com</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Obţineţi datele despre seriale de la TheTVDB.com</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Загрузка информации о ТВ-шоу с TheTVDB.com</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Skrapa för TV-seriemetadata från TVDB.com</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">Získať metadáta o televíznej relácii zo stránky TheTVDB.com</summary>
    <summary lang="sl">Prenesite informacije o TV serijah z TheTVDB.com</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">Hämta TV-seriemetadata från TVDB.com</summary>
    <summary lang="th">เรียกข้อมูลหลักของรายการทีวี จาก TheTVDB.com</summary>
    <summary lang="uk">Отримання відомостей про серіали із TheTVDB.com</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">从TheTVDB.com获取电视剧集信息</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">從 TheTVDB.com 取得電視節目資訊</summary>
    <description lang="af">TheTVDB.com is 'n TV Skraper. Die werf is 'n massiewe oop databasis wat deur enige iemand verander kan word en bevat vol meta data vir baie vertonings in verskillende tale. Alle inhoud en prente op die werf is bygedra deur sy gebruikers vir sy gebruikers en het 'n hoë standaard van kwaliteit. Die databasis skema en webruimte is oopbron onder die GPL.</description>
    <description lang="be">TheTVDB.com is a TV Scraper. The site is a massive open database that can be modified by anybody and contains full meta data for many shows in different languages. All content and images on the site have been contributed by their users for users and have a high standard or quality. The database schema and website are open source under the GPL.</description>
    <description lang="bg">TheTVDB.com предоставя информация за ТВ Сериали. Сайтът представлява една огромна, безплатна и отворена база от данни. Всеки може да редактира (наличната информация) или да добавя нова. Съдържа подробни данни за много сериали и на различни езици. Цялото съдържание на сайта и публикуваните изображения са предоставени от потребители за потребителите. Съдържанието на сайтът и базата от данни е с отворен код под лиценза GPL.</description>
    <description lang="cs">TheTVDB.com je zdroj metadat pro televizní pořady. Stránka je masivní otevřená databáze, kterou může kdokoliv upravovat a obsahuje veškerá metadata v různých jazycích k mnoha pořadům. Všechen obsah a obrázky jsou poskytnuty uživateli pro uživatele a mají vysokou kvalitu. Návrhový vzor databáze a webová stránka jsou svobodný software licencovaný pod GPL.</description>
    <description lang="da">TheTVDB.com er en TV-scraper. Siden er en massiv åben database, som alle kan modificere, og den indeholder fyldestgørende metadata for mange serier på forskellige sprog. Alt indhold og alle billeder på siden er tilføjet af brugere og har en høj standard eller kvalitet. Databasens model og webside er open source under GPL.</description>
    <description lang="de">TheTVDB.com ist ein Scraper für TV-Serien. Die Seite hat eine riesige offene Datenbank, welche von jedem geändert werden kann. Sie enthält weitreichende Meta-Daten für viele TV-Serien in verschiedenen Sprachen. Alle Inhalte und Bilder dieser Seite stammen von User für User und haben eine hohe Qualität. Das Datenbankschema und die Webseite sind OpenSource unter dem GPL-Recht</description>
    <description lang="el">Το TVDB.com είναι ένα Scraper Τηλεόρασης. Η ιστοσελίδα είναι μία τεράστια ανοικτή βάση δεδομένων η οποία μπορεί να τροποποιηθεί από τον καθένα και περιέχει πλήρη μετα-δεδομένα για πολλές σειρές σε διάφορες γλώσσες. Όλο το περιεχόμενο και οι εικόνες στην ιστοσελίδα προέρχονται από τους χρήστες του, και έχουν υψηλά πρότυπα ποιότητας. Το σχήμα της βάσης δεδομένων και της ιστοσελίδας είναι ανοικτού κώδικα υπό το GPL.</description>
    <description lang="en">TheTVDB.com is a TV Scraper. The site is a massive open database that can be modified by anybody and contains full meta data for many shows in different languages. All content and images on the site have been contributed by their users for users and have a high standard or quality. The database schema and website are open source under the GPL.</description>
    <description lang="es">TheTVDB.com es un scraper de TV. El sitio es una enorme base de datos abierta que puede ser modificada por cualquiera y que contiene metadatos completos de muchas series en diferentes idiomas. Todos los contenidos e imágenes del sitio han sido aportados por sus usuarios y tienen una alta calidad. El esquema de base de datos y sitio web son de código abierto bajo la licencia GPL.</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">TheTVDB.com es un scraper de TV. El sitio es una enorme base de datos abierta que puede ser modificada por cualquiera y que contiene metadatos completos de muchas series en diferentes idiomas. Todos los contenidos e imágenes del sitio han sido aportados por sus usuarios y tienen una alta calidad. El esquema de base de datos y sitio web son de código abierto bajo la licencia GPL.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">TheTVDB.com es un scraper de series de TV. Este sitio es una base de datos masiva y abierta que puede ser modicada por cualquiera y contiene metadata completa para muchas series en diferentes lenguajes. Todo el contenido e imágenes del sitio han sido contribuidos por sus usuarios para usuarios, los cuales tienen un alto estándar de calidad. El esquema de la base de datos y el sitio web son de código abierto bajo GPL.</description>
    <description lang="fi">TheTVDB.com on TV-ohjelmatietojen lataaja. Sivusto on massiivinen avoin tietokanta, jonka tietoja kaikki pystyy muokkaamaan ja se sisältää täydet tiedot monista TV-ohjelmista usealla eri kielellä. Kaikki sivuston sisältö ja kuvat on korkealaatuisia ja käyttäjien lahjoittamia. Tietokanta ja sivusto ovat GPL-lisenssin alaisia.</description>
    <description lang="fr">TheTVDB.com est un collecteur TV. Le site est une immense base de données libre pouvant être modifiée par tout le monde et contenant toutes les informations de nombreuses séries en différentes langues. Les informations et images du site proviennent de contributions d'utilisateurs pour les usagers et sont d'excellentes qualités. Le schéma de la base de données et le site Web sont en open source sous licence GPL.</description>
    <description lang="gl">TheTVDB.com é un Scraper de TV. O sitio é unha enorme base de datos aberta que calquera pode modificar e contén todos os metadatos de centos de series en diferentes idiomas. Todo o contido e imaxes do sitio foi proporcionado polos seus usuarios e amosa un grande estándar de calidade. O esquema da base de datos e o sitio web son de código aberto baixo licenza GPL.</description>
    <description lang="he">TheTVDB.com הוא סקרייפר עבור תוכניות טלוויזיה. אתר זה הוא מסד נתונים פתוח עצום אשר כל אחד יכול לערוך ומכיל פרטים מלאים להרבה תוכניות טלוויזיה בשפות שונות. כל התכנים והתמונות באתר נתרמו ע"י המשתמשים שלה עבור משתמשים וישנו סטנדרט גבוה או איכות גבוהה. תכנית המסד נתונית והאתר הם בקוד פתוח תחת ה-GPL.</description>
    <description lang="hu">A TheTVDB.com egy TV műsor leolvasó. Az oldal egy hatalmas adatbázis amit bárki szabadon módosíthat és rengeteg TV műsor adatait tartalmazza különböző nyelveken. A minőségi tartalom és képanyag ezen az oldalon felhasználóktól származik más felhasználók számára. Az adatbázisstruktúra és a weblap nyílt forráskódú a GPL licenc alatt.</description>
    <description lang="it">TheTVDB.com è uno scraper di programmi TV. Questo sito è un enorme database che può essere modificato da chiunque, e contiene tutte le informazioni di molti show in varie lingue. Tutti i contenuti e le immagini sul sito sono stati forniti dagli utenti, ed hanno un alto standard di qualità. Lo schema del database e il sito internet sono open source sotto licenza GPL.</description>
    <description lang="ja">TheTVDB.com は TV スクレーパーです。本サイトは強力でオープンなデータベースで、誰もが追加修正可能です。テレビ番組のメタデータは多くの言語で提供されています。番組情報や画像データはユーザにより提供され、そのクオリティは非常に高いものです。データベーススキーマと web サイトは GPL ライセンスのオープンソースです。</description>
    <description lang="ko">TheTVDB.com 은 TV 자료수집기입니다. 위 사이트는 이용자가 직접 수정할 수 있으며 다양한 언어의 완전한 메타 데이터를 포함하는 방대한 오픈 데이터베이스입니다. 사이트의 모든 콘텐츠와 이미지들은 사이트 이용자들이 다른 이용자들을 위해 제공한 것이며 높은 품질을 가지고 있습니다. 웹사이트와 데이터베이스 스키마는 GLP 오픈소스입니다.</description>
    <description lang="lt">TheTVDB.com yra TV Scraper. Ši svetainė yra didžiulė atvira duomenų bazė, kuria gali pakeisti bet kas ir kurioje visa meta duomenis bazė daugelo šou įvairiomis kalbomis. Visas svetainės turinys atnaujinamas/papyldomasvartotojų ir turi aukštą kokybės standartą. Duomenų bazės ir svetainės yra atviro kodo pagal GPL standartą.</description>
    <description lang="mk">TheTVDB.com is a TV Scraper. The site is a massive open database that can be modified by anybody and contains full meta data for many shows in different languages. All content and images on the site have been contributed by their users for users and have a high standard or quality. The database schema and website are open source under the GPL.</description>
    <description lang="nl">TheTVDB.com is een seriescraper. De site is een gigantische open databank die iedereen kan aanpassen en uitbreiden, en biedt metadata aan voor TV-series in verschillende talen. Alle inhoud en afbeeldingen zijn afkomstig van gebruikers en moeten een grondige kwaliteitscontrole doorstaan. Het databankschema en de websitecode zijn vrijgegeven onder de open source GPL-licentie.</description>
    <description lang="pl">TheTVDB.com jest scraperem TV. Ten serwis jest ogromną, wielojęzykową i otwartą bazą danych o serialach, którą może edytować każdy. Zawartość tego serwisu została dostarczona przez użytkowników, dla użytkowników. Dostępne materiały są najwyższej jakości.</description>
    <description lang="pt">O TheTVDB.com é um scraper para séries TV. O site é uma gigantesca base de dados livre que pode ser alterada por qualquer pessoa e contém informação em várias línguas. Todos os conteúdos do site foram enviados por utilizadores e têm um elevado padrão de qualidade. A base de dados e o site funcionam sob uma licença GPL de software livre.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">TheTVDB.com é um scraper de seriados. O site é um enorme banco de dados aberto que pode ser modificado por qualquer pessoa e contém metadados completos de muitos seriados em diferentes idiomas. Todos os conteúdos e imagens no site foram contribuições de usuários para usuários e têm um alto padrão de qualidade. O esquema do banco de dados e do site são de código aberto sob a licença GPL.</description>
    <description lang="ro">TheTVDB.com este un colectore TV. Site-ul este o bază de date masivă, deschisă, ce poate fi modificată de oricine şi conţine date complete despre multe seriale în diferite limbi. Tot conţinutul site-ului a fost contribuit de către utilizatori pentru utilizatori şi are un standard de caliate înalt. Schema bazei de date şi site-ul au sursele libere sub licenţă GPL.</description>
    <description lang="ru">TheTVDB.com — это инфоресурс для сериалов. Сайт представляет собой огромную открытую базу данных, в которую может вносить данные любой пользователь и которая содержит полные мета-данные для многих сериалов на различных языках. Всё содержимое и изображения на сайте были выложены его пользователями для других пользователей и имеют высокий уровень качества. Структура базы данных и веб-сайт созданы с открытым исходным кодом по лицензии GPL.</description>
    <description lang="se">TVDB.com är en TV-skrapa. Sajten är en massiv öppen databas som kan ändras av vem som helst och innehåller full metadata för mängder av serier på olika språk. Allt innehåll och bilder på sajten har bidragits av användare för användare och har en hög standard eller kvalitet. Databasschemat och webbsidan är licensierat som GPL.</description>
    <description lang="sk">TheTVDB.com je zdroj získavania dát ohľadom TV. Táto stránka je obrovskou otvorenou databázou, ktorú môže upravovať ktokoľvek a obsahuje úplne metadáta pre mnoho relácií v rôznych jazykoch. Všetok obsah a obrázky na stránke bol dodaný samotnými používateľmi pre používateľov a udržuje si vysoký štandard a kvalitu. Schéma databázy a webová stránka sú dostupné vo forme open source v súlade s licenciou GPL.</description>
    <description lang="sl">TheTVDB.com je ponudnik informacij o TV serijah. Stran je masovna odprta baza podatkov, ki jo lahko dopolni kdorkoli, in vsebuje informacije o najrazličnejših TV serijah v več jezikih. Vsa vsebina in slike so bile dodane s strani uporabnikov in imajo visok nivo kvalitete. Shema baze in spletna stran sta odprtokodni pod GPL.</description>
    <description lang="sv">TVDB.com är en TV-skrapa. Sajten är en massiv öppen databas som kan bli modifierad av vem som helst och innehåller all metadata för många serier på olika språk. Allt innehåll och bilder på sidan har bidragits av användare för användare och har hög standard eller kvalitet. Databasschemat och sidan är öppen källkod licensierat under GPL.</description>
    <description lang="th">TheTVDB.com เป็นตัวดึงข้อมูลทีวี เว็บไซต์เป็นฐานข้อมูลเปิดขนาดใหญ่ที่สามารถแก้ไขได้โดยทุกคนและมีข้อมูลขั้นสูงเต็มรูปแบบ สำหรับหลาย ๆ รายการ ในแต่ละภาษาที่แตกต่างกัน เนื้อหาและรูปภาพทั้งหมดในเว็บไซต์ ได้รับการสนับสนุนโดยผู้ใช้เพื่อผู้ใช้ มีคุณภาพและมาตรฐานที่สูง schemaของฐานข้อมูลและเว็บไซต์ได้เปิดภายใต้ GPL</description>
    <description lang="zh">TheTVDB.com是一个电视刮削器。该网站是一个巨大的开放式数据库，任何人都可以修改，包含多语言的许多电视剧集资料。网站设定了高品质标准，所有图片和内容都由用户提供。数据库结构和网站均在GPL许可下开源。</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.digitalprom" name="DPMC Addons repository" version="1.0.1" provider-name="digitalprom">
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="DPMC Addons repository">
		<info compressed="false">http://digitalprom-mc-repo.googlecode.com/git/master/addons/addons.xml</info>
		<checksum>http://digitalprom-mc-repo.googlecode.com/git/master/addons/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
		<datadir zip="false">http://digitalprom-mc-repo.googlecode.com/git/master/addons</datadir>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary>Digitalprom Mediacenter Official Addons Repository</summary>
		<description>DPMC addons updates and new addons</description>
		<disclaimer>An official DPMC addons only</disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.pil"
       name="Python Image Library"
       version="1.1.7"
       provider-name="PythonWare">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
             library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.pysqlite"
       name="Python SQLite library hook"
       version="2.5.6"
       provider-name="Gerhard Haering">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
             library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.simplejson"
       name="simplejson"
       version="2.0.10"
       provider-name="code.google.com/simplejson">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
             library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon
  id="visualization.dxspectrum"
  version="1.0.2"
  name="DirectX Spectrum"
  provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <extension
    point="xbmc.player.musicviz"
    library_windx="Spectrum_win32dx.vis"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af">Visualisering wat 'n roterende 3D Spektrum Analiseerder vertoon</summary>
    <summary lang="ar">تصور عرض محلل طيف دوار 3 الأبعاد</summary>
    <summary lang="be">Visualisation showing a rotating 3D Spectrum Analyzer</summary>
    <summary lang="bg">Визуализация представяща ротиращ се 3D спектрален анализатор</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">Efecte visual que mostra un analitzador d'espectre en 3D rotant</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">Vizualizace zobrazující rotující 3D spektrální analyzátor</summary>
    <summary lang="da">Visualisering der viser en roterende 3D-spektrumanalyse</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Diese Visualisierung zeigt eine rotierende Spektrumanalyse in 3D</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Οπτικοποίηση που εμφανίζει έναν περιστρεφόμενο τρισδιάστατο Αναλυτή Φάσματος</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Visualisation showing a rotating 3D Spectrum Analyzer</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Visualización que muestra un analizador de espectro en 3D girando</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Visualización que muestra un analizador de espectro en 3D girando</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Visualización mostrando un Analizador de Espectro en 3D</summary>
    <summary lang="et">Pöörlevat 3D spektraalanalüüsi näitav visuaal</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">Pyörivä 3D-spektrianalysaattori</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Visualisation affichant un analyseur de spectre 3D en rotation</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">Visualización que amosa un analizador de espe</summary>
    <summary lang="he">DirectX Spectrum זהו חיזוי אשר מציג סיבובי 3D Spectrum Analyzer</summary>
    <summary lang="hr">Vizualizacija koja prikazuje rotirajući 3D spektralni analizator</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Vizualizáció 3D spektrum analizátorral</summary>
    <summary lang="is">Myndskreyting sem sýnir þrívíddar rófgreini</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Visualizzazione che mostra un analizzatore di spettro 3D ruotante</summary>
    <summary lang="ja">回転する 3D スペクトラムアナライザーを表示する DirectX ビジュアライザー</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">회전하는 3D 스펙트럼 분석기를 보여지는 음악시각화</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">Vizualizacija rodo rotacinis 3D spektro analizatorių</summary>
    <summary lang="mk">Оваа визуализација покажува ротирачки 3Д анализатор на спектар</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">DirectX-visualisatie die een roterende 3D-spectrumanalyse weergeeft</summary>
    <summary lang="no">Visualisering som viser en roterende 3D spektrumanalysator</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Wizualizacja pokazująca obracający się analizator widma w 3D (DirectX)</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Visualização que mostra um analisador espectral rotativo em 3D</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Visualização que mostra um analisador espectral rotativo em 3D </summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Vizualizare care afișează un analizor de spectre 3D rotativ</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Визуализация, показывающая вращающийся трёхмерный анализатор спектра</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">Vizualizácia zobrazujúca rotujúci 3D Spektrálny analyzér</summary>
    <summary lang="sl">Vizualizacija, ki prikazuje vrtečo 3D spektralno analizo</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">Visualisering som visar en roterande 3D-spektrumanalysator</summary>
    <summary lang="th">การแสดงแสงสี ทำให้เห็นการหมุนแบบ 3 มิติ ของการวิเคราะห์คลื่นความถี่เสียง</summary>
    <summary lang="uk">Візуалізація що показує обертаючийся 3D спектроаналізатор.</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">显示旋转三维频谱分析图像的可视化效果</summary>
    <description lang="af">DirectX Spectrum is 'n Visualisering wat 'n roterende 3D Spektrum Analiseerder, verbeeld met DirectX, vertoon wat op die maat van die musiek beweeg en 'n golf effek oor die spektrum rooster skep.&#10;Dit het ook verstellings vir die aanpas van spektrum staaf hoogte, sy spoed, en hoe die stawe verbeeld word (solied, punte, draad raamwerk) en is 'n lekker ligte, lae cpu verbruik visualisering wat fantasties lyk</description>
    <description lang="ar">طيف دايركت اكس هو عرض تخيل دوار 3 الأبعاد مقدم بدايركت اكس الذي يتحرك مع وقع الموسيقى مُنشِأَ موجة تأثير عبر شبكة الطيف.&#10;وله أيضا إعدادات لتعديل شريط ارتفاع الطيف, و كيف الأشرطة تعرض (صلبة, نقط, سلكية) و لطيفة خفيفة الوزن, تصور بيدو رائع استخدام منخفض لوحدة المعالجة المركزية.</description>
    <description lang="be">DirectX Spectrum is a Visualisation showing a rotating 3D Spectrum Analyzer rendered in DirectX that moves to the beat of the music creating a wave effect across the spectrum grid.&#10;It also has settings to adjust the spectrum bar height, Its speed, and how the bars are rendered (solid, points, wire frame) and is a nice light weight, low cpu useage visualisation that looks great</description>
    <description lang="bg">DirectX Spectrum е визуализация изобразяваща ротиращ се 3D спектрален анализатор (рендването се извършва с DirectX). Ротацията е според ритъма на музиката и предизвиква вълнови ефект по спектрална решетка.&#10;Можете да настройвате височината на спектралните стълбове, скоростта и рендването - solid, points, wire frame. Характеризира се с отличен вид, като същевременно почти не натоварва процесора.</description>
    <description lang="ca">El DirectX Spectrum és una visualització que mostra un analitzador d'espectre rotant en 3D renderitzat en DirectX que es mou al ritme de la música i crea un efecte d'ona a través de la graella de l'espectre. També té ajustos per defniri l'alçada de la barra de l'espectre, la seva velocitat i la manera de renderitzar les barres (sòlid, punts, fil de ferro) i és una visualització lleugera, de poc ús de CPU que llueix be</description>
    <description lang="cs">DirectX Spectrum je vizualizace zobrazující rotující 3D spektrální analyzátor rendrovaný v DirectX, který se pohybuje v rytmu hudby a vytváří vlnový efekt napříč spektrální mřížkou.&#10;Obsahuje také nastavení pro přizpůsobení výšky sloupců spektra, rychlosti a způsobu vykreslení (vyplněný, body, drátový model). Je to velmi lehká vizualizace s nízkou zatíží CPU, která vypadá skvěle.</description>
    <description lang="da">DirectX Spektrum er en visualisering, der viser en roterende 3D-spektrumanalysator renderet i DirectX, som bevæger sig i takt til musikken og skaber en bølgeeffekt på tværs af spektrumfeltet.&#10;Den har også indstillinger til at justere spektrumliniens højde, fart og hvordan den bliver renderet (fast, punkter, trådramme). Det er en letvægtsvisualisering med lavt CPU-forbrug, som ser godt ud.</description>
    <description lang="de">DirectX Spectrum ist eine Visualisierung, die eine rotierende Spektrum Analyse in 3D zeigt. Die Visualisierung wird so gerendert, dass sie sich zum Takt der Musik bewegt und eine Welle über das Spektrum Grid legt. Es lässt sich neben der Höhe, die Geschwindigkeit als auch die Art der Balken (durchgehend, Punkte, Drahtgeflecht) einstellen. Eine schöne Visualisierung, die nur eine geringe CPU-Last erzeugt</description>
    <description lang="el">Το DirectX Spectrum είναι μία Οπτικοποίηση που εμφανίζει έναν περιστρεφόμενο τρισδιάστατο Αναλυτή Φάσματος που αποδίδεται μέσω DirectX και κινείται στο ρυθμό της μουσικής δημιουργώντας ένα κυματικό εφέ κατά μήκος του φασματικού πλέγματος.&#10;Διαθέτει ρυθμίσεις για τον ορισμό του ύψους των στηλών του φάσματος, του τρόπου απόδοσης των στηλών (συμπαγείς, σημειακές, συρματόπλεγμα), και είναι μία ελαφριά, εμφανίσιμη και χαμηλής υπολογιστικής ισχύος οπτικοποίηση</description>
    <description lang="en">DirectX Spectrum is a Visualisation showing a rotating 3D Spectrum Analyzer rendered in DirectX that moves to the beat of the music creating a wave effect across the spectrum grid.&#10;It also has settings to adjust the spectrum bar height, Its speed, and how the bars are rendered (solid, points, wire frame) and is a nice light weight, low cpu useage visualisation that looks great</description>
    <description lang="es">DirectX Spectrum es una visualización que muestra un analizador de espectro en 3D girando renderizado con DirectX que se mueve al ritmo de la música creando un efecto de onda en la rejilla del espectro.&#10;Se puede ajustar la altura de las barras, su velocidad, y como son renderizadas (sólido, puntos, malla). Es una visualización que utiliza poca CPU y muy agradable.</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">DirectX Spectrum es una visualización que muestra un analizador de espectro en 3D girando, renderizado con DirectX, que se mueve al ritmo de la música creando un efecto de onda en la rejilla del espectro.&#10;Se puede ajustar la altura de las barras, su velocidad, y como son renderizadas (sólido, puntos, malla). Es una visualización que utiliza poca CPU y muy agradable.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">Espectro DirectX es una Visualización que muestra un Analizador de Especto en 3D rotando renderizado en DirectX que se mueve al ritmo de la música creando un efecto de onda a través del espectro de la red.&#10;También tiene configuraciones para ajustar la altura de la barra de espectro, su velocidad, y cómo las barras son renderizadas (sólidas, puntos, malla de alambre) y es una buena visualización liviana, de poco uso de cpu que se ve genial.</description>
    <description lang="et">DirectX Spectrum on visuaal, mis näitab pöörlevat 3D spektraalanalüüsi, mis on renderdatud DirectC keskkonnas ja mis liigub muusika rütmis luues laineefekti üle spektraalvõrgu.&#10;Lisaks on sellel võimalus muuta spektri kõrgust, selle kiirust ja kuidas ribasid renderdatakse (tahkis, punktid, sõrestik). DirectX Spectrum on ilusa väljanägemisega kerge ja väikese protsessorikasutusega visuaal.</description>
    <description lang="fi">Näyttää pyörivän 3D-spektrianalysaattorin, joka liikkuu musiikin tahdissa tuottaen aaltotehosteen spektrikuvaajaan.&#10;Spektripalkin korkeuden, nopeuden, ja piirtotavan (täytetyt, pisteet, ääriviivat) voi asettaa asetuksista. Spectrum on kevyt visualisointi joka näyttää hyvältä.</description>
    <description lang="fr">DirectX Spectrum est une visualisation affichant un analyseur de spectre 3D en rotation, sous DirectX. Il réagit au rythme de la musique, créant un effet d'onde sur la grille du spectre.&#10;Il propose divers paramètres pour ajuster la hauteur des barres du spectre, la vitesse, et le rendu des barres (plein, en points, en fil de fer). Une visualisation légère, peu gourmande en CPU et agréable à regarder.</description>
    <description lang="gl">DirectX Spectrum é unha Visualización que amosa un analizador de espectro rederizdo en DirectX que se move ó ritmo da música creando un efecto onda sobre a grella do espectro.&#10;Tamén ten configuracións para axustar a altura da barra do espectro, a súa velocidade e como as barras son renderizadas (sólidas, puntos, malla) e é unha visualización bonita, lixeira e de escaso consumo de CPU.</description>
    <description lang="he">DirectX Spectrum זהו חיזוי אשר מציג סיבובי 3D Spectrum Analyzer עובד דרך DirectX אשר זז לצלילי המוזיקה שיוצר אפקט גלים לרוחב רשת הספקטרום.&#10;יש אפשרות גם להגדיר את גובה פס הספקטרום, את המהירות, ואת התנהגות הפסים (filled, points, wire frame) וזהו חיזוי נחמד קל משקל לא מעמיס על המעבד ונראה נהדר.</description>
    <description lang="hr">DirectX Spectrum je vizualizacija koja prikazuje rotirajući 3D spektralni analizator renderiran u DirectX-u koji se pokreće u ritmu muzike stvarajući efekt valova u spektralnoj mreži.&#10;Također sadrži i postavke za namještanje visine sprektralnih traka, njihove brzine, i načina na koji su prikazane (popunjeno, točke, žičani okvir). Vizualizacija izgleda sjajno te je malih memorijskih i CPU zahtjeva.</description>
    <description lang="hu">A DirectX Spectrum egy olyan vizualizáció ami egy 3D hang spektrum analizátort mutat DirectX segítségével megjelenítve, ami a zene ritmusára mozog egy hullám-effektust képezve a teljes spektrumhálón.&#10;Beállítható a spektrum oszlopok magassága, mozgási sebessége és hogy az oszlopok hogyan jelenjenek meg (teli, pontok, drótváz). Ez egy kis erőforrásigényű vizualizáció ami nagyon jól mutat.</description>
    <description lang="is">DirectX Spectrum er myndskreyting sem sýnir þrívíddar rófgreini sem snýst sem er teiknaður í DirectX og hreyfist í takt við tónlistina sem myndar bylgjuhreyfingu yfir rófið.&#10;Það er líka hægt að stilla hæð mælingana, hraða og hvernig þær eru teiknaðar (fyllt, punktar, útlínur) myndskrytingin setur lítið álag á örgjörva og lítur vel út</description>
    <description lang="it">DirectX Spectrum è una visualizzazione che mostra un analizzatore di spettro 3D ruotante renderizzato in DirectX che si muove a tempo di musica creando un effetto onda tramite la griglia di spettro.&#10;Ha anche varie impostazioni: altezza delle barra dello spettro, la sua velocità e come le barre sono renderizzate (solidi, punti, reticolato). E' una visualizzazione leggera, che richiede poche risorse cpu e dall'aspetto fantastico</description>
    <description lang="ja">DirectX Spectrum is a Visualisation showing a rotating 3D Spectrum Analyzer rendered in DirectX that moves to the beat of the music creating a wave effect across the spectrum grid.&#10;It also has settings to adjust the spectrum bar height, Its speed, and how the bars are rendered (solid, points, wire frame) and is a nice light weight, low cpu useage visualisation that looks great</description>
    <description lang="ko">DirectX 스펙트럼은 회전하는 3D 스펙트럼 분석기를 통해 음악시각화를 보여주며 음악의 비트가 만들어내는 웨이브 효과를 스펙트럼 그리드에 보여줍니다. 설정에서 스펙트럼 바의 높이, 속도, 바의 갯수 (채워짐, 점, 와이어 프레임)를 지정할수 있습니다. 가볍고 CPU를 많이 사용하지 않습니다.</description>
    <description lang="lt">DirectX spektro vizualizacija, kurioje besisukantį 3D spektro analizatorių, paimta iš DirectX, katras juda į muzikos ritmą, įteigiančio bangų poveikį visame spektro tinklelyje.&#10;Turi nustatymuose nureguliuoti spektro juostos aukštį, jo greitį, teikiamas kraštines (kieta, taškai, tinklelio rėmas),vizualizacijai naudoja mažai CPU</description>
    <description lang="mk">DirectX Spectrum is a Visualisation showing a rotating 3D Spectrum Analyzer rendered in DirectX that moves to the beat of the music creating a wave effect across the spectrum grid.⏎ It also has settings to adjust the spectrum bar height, Its speed, and how the bars are rendered (solid, points, wire frame) and is a nice light weight, low cpu useage visualisation that looks great</description>
    <description lang="nl">DirectX-spectrum toont een roterende 3D-spectrumanalyse via DirectX. Het beweegt mee op de maat van de muziek, waarbij een golfeffect ontstaat over het spectrumraster.&#10;U kunt de hoogte, snelheid en weergave (vol, stippen, ...) van de spectrumbalk zelf instellen. Deze visualisatie vereist weinig geheugen en belast de processor nauwelijks.</description>
    <description lang="no">DirectX Spectrum er en visualisering som viser en 3D spektrumanalysator rendret i DirectX som beveger seg i takt med musikken å skaper en bølge effekt.&#10;Du kan også stille in spektrums bar høyden, hastigheten og hvordan barene blir rendret (solid, punkt, trådramme) og er veldig letvekt, bruker lite cpu og ser flott ut</description>
    <description lang="pl">Wizualizacja pokazuje obracający się, trójwymiarowy analizator widma, renderowany przy użyciu DirectX. Możesz ustawić wysokość słupków, ich prędkość i wygląd.</description>
    <description lang="pt">O DirectX Spectrum é uma visualização que mostra um analisador espectral rotativo em 3D, renderizado em DirectX, que se sincroniza com o ritmo da música, criando assim um efeito de ondas na grelha espectral.&#10;Pode definir-se a altura das barras, a sua velocidade e como são renderizadas (sólido, pontos ou contorno). É uma visualização que não utiliza muito CPU e tem um aspecto fantástico.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">O DirectX Spectrum é uma visualização que mostra um analisador espectral rotacional 3d, renderizado em DirectX, que se sincroniza com a batida, criando assim um efeito de ondas na grelha espectral.&#10;Pode-se definir a altura das barras, a sua velocidade e como são renderizadas (sólido, pontos ou contorno). É uma visualização que utiliza pouco o CPU e com um visual fantástico</description>
    <description lang="ro">Spectrul DirectX este o vizualizare care afișează un analizor de spectre 3D rotativ randat în DirectX care se mișcă după bătăile muzicii creând un val dea-lungul grilei spectrale.&#10;De asemenea, are setări pentru ajustarea înălțimii bărilor spectrale, a vitezei, și a modului în care bările sunt randate (umplere, puncte, contur). Este o vizualizare cu consum redus al procesorului care arată fantastic de bine.</description>
    <description lang="ru">Эта визуализация на основе DirectX показывает вращающийся трёхмерный анализатор спектра, который движется в такт музыке, создавая эффект волны по всему спектру сетки.[C]&#10;Визуализация имеет настройки для регулировки высоты полос спектра, скорости движения и способа отображения полос (сплошной, точки, каркас), а также обладает небольшим размером и малой нагрузкой на процессор</description>
    <description lang="sk">DirectX Spectrum je vizualizácia zobrazujúca rotujúci 3D Spektrálny analyzér renderovaný v DirectX, ktorý sa pohybuje do rytmu hudby a vytvára vlnový efekt.&#10;Môžte si tiež nastaviť jeho výšku, rýchlosť a metódu renderovania(pevné, body, wireframe) a je to veľmi jednoduchá, málo procesor zaťažujúca vizualizácia, ktorá vyzerá skvelo</description>
    <description lang="sl">DirectX Spectrum je vizualizacija, ki prikazuje vrtečo 3D spektralno analizo, generirano v DirectX, ki se premika v ritmu glasbe in ustvarja učinek valovanja v celotnem spektru.&#10;Vsebuje tudi nastavitve za prilagoditev višine spektra, hitrosti in oblike (polno, točke, okvir) ter je varčna vizualizacija, z nizko porabo CPU-ja, ki izgleda super</description>
    <description lang="sv">DirectX-spektrum är en visualisering som visar en roterande 3D-spektrumanalysator renderad i DirectX. Den rör sig till musikens takt och skapar en vågeffekt över spektrat.&#10;Den har också inställningar för att justera staplarnas höjd, deras hastighet, hur de ska visas (solida, punkter, ramverk) och är en visualisering med låg cpu-användning samtidigt som den ser bra ut</description>
    <description lang="th">DirectX Spectrum เป็น การแสดงแสงสี ทำให้เห็นการหมุนกราฟวิเคราะห์คลื่นความถี่เสียง แบบ 3 มิติ ที่สร้างขึ้นโดย DirectX ที่ขยับไปตามจังหวะของเพลงที่สร้างผลกระทบเป็นคลื่นไปทั่วตารางความถี่.&#10;นอกจากนี้ยังมีการตั้งค่าเพื่อปรับความสูงของแท่งคลื่นความถี่,ความเร็วและกระบวนการที่แท่งแสดงผล (ของแข็ง, จุด, โครงลวด) ทั้งยังใช้ทรัพยากรน้อยได้ดี, การแสดงแสงสี ที่ใช้ซีพียูต่ำนั่นก็ดูยอดเยี่ยมทีเดียว</description>
    <description lang="uk">DirectX Spectrum  є візалізаціє що показує обертаючийся 3D спектроаналізатор що промальовується з використанням технології  DirectX. Спектроаналізатор показує стовпчики змінної висоти що рухаються в такт з музикою і створюють ефект подібний до хвилі.&#10;Ви маєте можливість налаштувати висоту стовпчиків, їх швидкість і те як вони намальовані (Заповнені, контури, крапки). Це досить проста, і невимоглива до процесора візуалізація, але яка має чудовий вигляд.</description>
    <description lang="zh">DirectX Spectrum可视化效果是DirectX渲染的一个旋转的三维频谱分析图像，频谱矩阵随着音乐节拍而象波浪起伏。&#10;你还可以设置频谱棒的高度、变换速度、以及呈现效果（固体、点、框架）。这是一个不错的轻量级，低CPU使用率的可视化效果。</description>
    <platform>windx</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon
  id="visualization.fishbmc"
  version="4.0.1"
  name="FishBMC"
  provider-name="26elf">
  <extension
    point="xbmc.player.musicviz"
    library_linux="fishbmc.vis"
    library_osx="fishbmc.vis"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">Visualisation showing Waves and Blur Effects</summary>
    <description lang="en">fishBMC is based on fische, a standalone sound visualisation tool. The basic principle is: draw the waveform and smear the drawing along predefined vectors. However fische also incorporates advanced beat detection, which really guarantees a great visual experience.</description>
    <disclaimer>If this breaks anything, the pieces remain yours.</disclaimer>
    <platform>linux osx</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon
  id="visualization.glspectrum"
  version="1.0.2"
  name="OpenGL Spectrum"
  provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <extension
    point="xbmc.player.musicviz"
    library_linux="opengl_spectrum.vis"
    library_osx="opengl_spectrum.vis"
    library_android="libvisopengl_spectrum.so" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af">Visualisering wys a roterende 3D Spektrum Analiseerder</summary>
    <summary lang="ar">عارض يظهر طيف محلل دوري ثلاثي الأبعاد</summary>
    <summary lang="be">Visualisation showing a rotating 3D Spectrum Analyzer</summary>
    <summary lang="bg">Визуализация представяща ротиращ се 3D спектрален анализатор</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">Visualització mostrant un analitzador d'espectre giratori 3D</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">Vizualizace zobrazující rotující 3D spektrální analyzátor</summary>
    <summary lang="da">Visualisering der viser en roterende 3D-spektrumanalyse</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Diese Visualisierung zeigt eine rotierende Spektrum Analyse in 3D</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Οπτικοποίηση που εμφανίζει έναν περιστρεφόμενο τρισδιάστατο Αναλυτή Φάσματος</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Visualisation showing a rotating 3D Spectrum Analyzer</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Visualización que muestra un analizador de espectro en 3D girando</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Visualización que muestra un analizador de espectro en 3D girando</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Visualización que muestra un Analizador de Espectro giratorio 3D</summary>
    <summary lang="et">Visuaal, mis näitab pöörlevat 3D spektraalanalüüsi</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">Pyörivä 3D-spektrianalysaattori</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Visualisation affichant un analyseur de spectre 3D en rotation</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">Visualización que amosa un analizador de espectro virando en 3D</summary>
    <summary lang="he">DirectX Spectrum זהו חיזוי אשר מציג סיבובי 3D Spectrum Analyzer</summary>
    <summary lang="hr">Vizualizacija koja prikazuje rotirajući 3D spektralni analizator</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Vizualizáció 3D spektrum analizátorral</summary>
    <summary lang="is">Myndskreyting sem sýnir þrívíddar rófgreini</summary>
    <summary lang="it">La visualizzazione mostra un analizzatore di spettro 3D rotante</summary>
    <summary lang="ja">回転する 3D スペクトラムアナライザーを表示する OpenGL ビジュアライザー</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">회전하는 3D 스펙트럼 분석기를 보여지는 음악시각화</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">Vizualizacija rodo rotacinis 3D spektro analizatorių</summary>
    <summary lang="mk">Визуализација која покажува ротирачки 3Д анализатор на спектар</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">DirectX-visualisatie die een roterende 3D-spectrumanalyse weergeeft</summary>
    <summary lang="no">Visualisering som viser en roterende 3D ​​Spectrum Analyzer</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Wizualizacja pokazująca obracający się analizator widma w 3D</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Visualização que mostra um analisador espectral rotativo em 3D</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Visualização que mostra um analisador espectral rotativo em 3D</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Vizualizare cu afișarea unui analizor de spectru 3D rotativ</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Визуализация, показывающая вращающийся трёхмерный анализатор спектра</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">Vizualizácia zobrazujúca rotujúci 3D spektrálny analyzátor</summary>
    <summary lang="sl">Vizualizacija, ki prikatuje vrtečo 3D spektralno analizo</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">Visualisering som visar en roterande 3D-spektrumanalysator</summary>
    <summary lang="th">การแสดงแสงสี ทำให้เห็นการหมุนแบบ 3 มิติ ของการวิเคราะห์คลื่นความถี่เสียง</summary>
    <summary lang="uk">Візуалізація що показує обертаючийся 3D спектроаналізатор.</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">显示旋转三维频谱分析图像的可视化效果</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">顯示旋轉的3D頻譜分析視覺效果</summary>
    <description lang="af">Opengl Spectrum is 'n Visualisering wat 'n roterende 3D Spektrum Analiseerder, verbeeld met Opengl, vertoon wat op die maat van die musiek beweeg en 'n golf effek oor die spektrum rooster skep.&#10;Dit het ook verstellings vir die aanpas van spektrum staaf hoogte, sy spoed, en hoe die stawe verbeeld word (solied, punte, draad raamwerk) en is 'n lekker ligte, lae cpu verbruik visualisering wat fantasties lyk</description>
    <description lang="ar">طيف Opengl هو تحليل بصري متحرك ثلاثي الابعاد للموسيقى! يتحرك بواسطة يرنامج Opengl على وزن الموسيقى في شكل موجة.&#10;توجد ايضا اعدادات لتعديل شبكة الطيف من حيث طول الاعمدة, سرعتها, وحتى شكلها (صلبة, نقاط, اسلاك) تعمل هذة بحمل خفيف, ومعالجة cpu ضئيلة لكنها تبدو رائعة</description>
    <description lang="be">Opengl Spectrum is a Visualisation showing a rotating 3D Spectrum Analyzer rendered in Opengl that moves to the beat of the music creating a wave effect across the spectrum grid.&#10;It also has settings to adjust the spectrum bar height, Its speed, and how the bars are rendered (solid, points, wire frame) and is a nice light weight, low cpu useage visualisation that looks great</description>
    <description lang="bg">Opengl Spectrum е визуализация изобразяваща ротиращ се 3D спектрален анализатор (рендването се извършва с Opengl). Ротацията е според ритъма на музиката и предизвиква вълнови ефект по спектрална решетка.&#10;Можете да настройвате височината на спектралните стълбове, скоростта и рендването - solid, points, wire frame. Характеризира се с отличен вид, като същевременно почти не натоварва процесора.</description>
    <description lang="ca">OpenGL Spectrum és una visualització que mostra un analitzador d'espectre giratori en 3D renderitzat amb OpenGL que es mou al ritme de la música creant un efecte d'ona al llarg de la graella de l'espectre.⏎ També té opcions per ajustar l'alçada de la barra de l'espectre, la seva velocitat, i com es renderitzen les barres (sòlid, punts, malla de filferro). Una visualització que utilitza poca CPU i que és veu molt bé. </description>
    <description lang="cs">Opengl Spectrum je vizualizace zobrazující rotující 3D spektrální analyzátor rendrovaný v OpenGL, který se pohybuje v rytmu hudby a vytváří vlnový efekt napříč spektrální mřížkou.&#10;Obsahuje také nastavení pro přizpůsobení výšky sloupců spektra, rychlosti a způsobu vykreslení (vyplněný, body, drátový model). Je to velmi lehká vizualizace s nízkou zatíží CPU, která vypadá skvěle.</description>
    <description lang="da">OpenGL-spektrum er en visualisering, der viser en roterende 3D-spektrumanalysator renderet i DirectX, som bevæger sig i takt til musikken og skaber en bølgeeffekt på tværs af spektrumfeltet.&#10;Den har også indstillinger til at justere spektrumliniens højde, fart og hvordan den bliver renderet (fast, punkter, trådramme). Det er en letvægtsvisualisering med lavt CPU-forbrug, som ser godt ud.</description>
    <description lang="de">Opengl Spectrum ist eine Visualisierung, die eine rotierende Spektrum Analyse in 3D zeigt. Die Visualisierung wird so gerendert, dass sie sich zum Takt der Musik bewegt und eine Welle über das Spektrum Grid legt.&#10;Es lässt sich neben der Höhe, die Geschwindigkeit als auch die Art der Balken (durchgehend, Punkte, Drahtgeflecht) einstellen. Eine schöne Visualisierung, die nur eine geringe CPU-Last erzeugt</description>
    <description lang="el">Το Opengl Spectrum είναι μία Οπτικοποίηση που εμφανίζει έναν περιστρεφόμενο τρισδιάστατο Αναλυτή Φάσματος που αποδίδεται μέσω Opengl και κινείται στο ρυθμό της μουσικής δημιουργώντας ένα κυματικό εφέ κατά μήκος του φασματικού πλέγματος.&#10;Διαθέτει ρυθμίσεις για τον ορισμό του ύψους των στηλών του φάσματος, του τρόπου απόδοσης των στηλών (συμπαγείς, σημειακές, συρματόπλεγμα), και είναι μία ελαφριά, εμφανίσιμη και χαμηλής υπολογιστικής ισχύος οπτικοποίηση</description>
    <description lang="en">Opengl Spectrum is a Visualisation showing a rotating 3D Spectrum Analyzer rendered in Opengl that moves to the beat of the music creating a wave effect across the spectrum grid.&#10;It also has settings to adjust the spectrum bar height, Its speed, and how the bars are rendered (solid, points, wire frame) and is a nice light weight, low cpu useage visualisation that looks great</description>
    <description lang="es">OpenGL Spectrum es una visualización que muestra un analizador de espectro en 3D girando renderizado con OpenGL que se mueve al ritmo de la música creando un efecto de onda en la rejilla del espectro.&#10;Se puede ajustar la altura de las barras, su velocidad, y como son renderizadas (sólido, puntos, malla). Es una visualización que utiliza poca CPU y muy agradable.</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">OpenGL Spectrum es una visualización que muestra un analizador de espectro en 3D girando, renderizado con OpenGL, que se mueve al ritmo de la música creando un efecto de onda en la rejilla del espectro.&#10;Se puede ajustar la altura de las barras, su velocidad, y como son renderizadas (sólido, puntos, malla). Es una visualización que utiliza poca CPU y muy agradable.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">Espectro Opengl es una Visualización que muestra un Analizador de Especto en 3D rotando renderizado en Opengl que se mueve al ritmo de la música creando un efecto de onda a través del espectro de la red.&#10;También tiene configuraciones para ajustar la altura de la barra de espectro, su velocidad, y cómo las barras son renderizadas (sólidas, puntos, malla de alambre) y es una buena visualización liviana, de poco uso de cpu que se ve genial.</description>
    <description lang="et">Opengl Spectrum on visuaal, mis näitab 3D spektraalanalüüsi renderdatud Opengl'is, mis liigub liigub muusika rütmis luues laineefekti üle spektraalvõrgustiku.&#10;Lisaks on olemas ka võimalus seadistada spektri kõrgust, selle kiirust ja kuidas ribasid renderdatakse (tahkis, punktid, sõrestik). Opengl Spectrum on hea väljanägemisega kerge ja vähese protsessorikasutusega visuaal.</description>
    <description lang="fi">Näyttää pyörivän 3D-spektrianalysaattorin, joka liikkuu musiikin tahdissa tuottaen aaltotehosteen spektrikuvaajaan.&#10;Spektripalkin korkeuden, nopeuden, ja piirtotavan (täytetyt, pisteet, ääriviivat) voi asettaa asetuksista. Spectrum on kevyt visualisointi joka näyttää hyvältä.</description>
    <description lang="fr">Opengl Spectrum est une visualisation affichant un analyseur de spectre 3D en rotation, sous Opengl. Il réagit au rythme de la musique, créant un effet d'onde sur la grille du spectre.&#10;Il propose divers paramètres pour ajuster la hauteur, la vitesse, et le rendu des barres du spectre (plein, points, fil de fer). Une visualisation légère, peu gourmande en CPU et agréable à regarder.</description>
    <description lang="gl">Opengl Spectrum é unha Visualización que amosa un analizador de espectro virando en 3D renderizado con OpenGL que se move ó ritmo da música creando un efecto de onde ó longo da grella do espectro.&#10;Tamén ten opcións para axustar a altura da barra, a velocidade e como se renderizan as barras (sólidas, puntos, malla) do espectro. É bonito, lixeiro, de baixo custo en CPU.</description>
    <description lang="he">Opengl Spectrum זהו חיזוי אשר מציג סיבובי 3D Spectrum Analyzer אשר זז לצלילי המוזיקה שיוצר אפקט גלים לרוחב רשת הספקטרום.&#10;יש אפשרות גם להגדיר את גובה פס הספקטרום, את המהירות, ואת התנהגות הפסים (filled, points, wire frame) וזהו חיזוי נחמד קל משקל לא מעמיס על המעבד ונראה נהדר.</description>
    <description lang="hr">Opengl Spectrum je vizualizacija koja prikazuje rotirajući 3D spektralni analizator renderiran u Opengl-u koji se pokreće u ritmu muzike stvarajući efekt valova u spektralnoj mreži.&#10;Također sadrži i postavke za namještanje visine sprektralnih traka, njihove brzine, i načina na koji su prikazane (popunjeno, točke, žičani okvir). Vizualizacija izgleda sjajno te je malih memorijskih i CPU zahtjeva.</description>
    <description lang="hu">Az Opengl Spectrum egy olyan vizualizáció ami egy 3D hang spektrum analizátort mutat Opengl segítségével megjelenítve, ami a zene ritmusára mozog egy hullám-effektust képezve a teljes spektrumhálón.&#10;Beállítható a spektrum oszlopok magassága, mozgási sebessége és hogy az oszlopok hogyan jelenjenek meg (teli, pontok, drótváz). Ez egy kis erőforrásigényű vizualizáció ami nagyon jól mutat.</description>
    <description lang="is">Opengl Spectrum er myndskreyting sem sýnir þrívíddar rófgreini sem snýst sem er teiknaður í Opengl og hreyfist í takt við tónlistina sem myndar bylgjuhreyfingu yfir rófið.&#10;Það er líka hægt að stilla hæð mælingana, hraða og hvernig þær eru teiknaðar (fyllt, punktar, útlínur) myndskrytingin setur lítið álag á örgjörva og lítur vel út</description>
    <description lang="it">Opengl Spectrum è una visualizzazione che mostra un analizzatore di spettro renderizzato in Opengl che si muove a tempo di musica creando un effetto onda attraverso la griglia.&#10;E' possibile regolare varie impostazioni: l'altezza delle barre, la velocità di risposta e come le barre sono renderizzate (piene, con punti o con righe). E' una visualizzazione rilassante e con basso uso del processore.</description>
    <description lang="ja">Opengl Spectrum is a Visualisation showing a rotating 3D Spectrum Analyzer rendered in Opengl that moves to the beat of the music creating a wave effect across the spectrum grid.&#10;It also has settings to adjust the spectrum bar height, Its speed, and how the bars are rendered (solid, points, wire frame) and is a nice light weight, low cpu useage visualisation that looks great</description>
    <description lang="ko">Opengl 스펙트럼은 회전하는 3D 스펙트럼 분석기를 통해 음악시각화를 보여주며 음악의 비트가 만들어내는 웨이브 효과를 스펙트럼 그리드에 보여줍니다. 설정에서 스펙트럼 바의 높이, 속도, 바의 갯수 (채워짐, 점, 와이어 프레임)를 지정할수 있습니다. 가볍고 CPU를 많이 사용하지 않습니다.</description>
    <description lang="lt">Opengl spektro vizualizacija, kurioje besisukantį 3D spektro analizatorių, priimtą OpenGL, katras juda į muzikos ritmą, įsteigiantis bangų poveikį visame spektro tinklelyje.&#10;Taip pat turi nustatymus nureguliuoti spektro juostos aukštį, jos greitį, ir teikiamas kraštines (kieta, taškai, tinklelio rėmas) ir yra gražus bei lengvas, mažai naudoja CPU vizualizacijai, ir atrodo puikiai</description>
    <description lang="mk">Opengl Spectrum is a Visualisation showing a rotating 3D Spectrum Analyzer rendered in Opengl that moves to the beat of the music creating a wave effect across the spectrum grid.⏎ It also has settings to adjust the spectrum bar height, Its speed, and how the bars are rendered (solid, points, wire frame) and is a nice light weight, low cpu useage visualisation that looks great</description>
    <description lang="nl">Opengl Spectrum is een visualisatie met een draaiende 3D ​​Spectrum Analyzer gerenderd in OpenGL. Deze visualisatie beweegt op het ritme van de muziek en creëert een golf effect over het hele spectrum. ⏎&#10;Het heeft instellingen om de barhoogte en de snelheid aan te passen, en hoe de staven worden weergegeven (vast, punten, draad frame) en is een mooie lichtgewicht visualisatie die weinig van de cpu vraagt en er geweldig uit ziet.</description>
    <description lang="no">OpenGL Spectrum er en visualisering som viser et roterende 3D ​​Spectrum Analyzer gjengitt i OpenGL som flytter til rytmen i musikken skaper en bølge effekt over hele spekteret rutenettet.⏎&#10;Det har også innstillinger for å justere spekterets bar høyde, hastighet, og hvordan barene gjengis (solid, punkt, wireframe) og er en fin lett vekt, lav cpu brukende visualisering som ser flott ut</description>
    <description lang="pl">Wizualizacja pokazuje obracający się, trójwymiarowy analizator widma, renderowany przy użyciu OpenGL. Możesz ustawić wysokość słupków, ich prędkość i wygląd.</description>
    <description lang="pt">Opengl Spectrum é uma visualização que mostra um analisador espectral 3D rotativo, renderizado em Opengl, que se sincroniza com o ritmo da música, criando assim um efeito de ondas na grelha espectral.&#10;Pode-se definir a altura das barras, a sua velocidade e como são renderizadas (sólido, pontos ou contorno). É uma visualização que não utiliza muito CPU e tem um aspecto fantástico.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">O OpenGL Spectrum é uma visualização que mostra um analisador espectral rotativo 3D, renderizado em OpenGL, que se sincroniza com a batida, criando assim um efeito de ondas na grelha espectral.&#10;Pode-se definir a altura das barras, a sua velocidade e como são renderizadas (sólido, pontos ou contorno). É uma visualização que utiliza pouco o CPU e com um visual fantástico.</description>
    <description lang="ro">Spectrul OpenGL este o vizualizare care afișează un analizor de spectre 3D rotativ randat în OpenGL care se mișcă după bătăile muzicii creând un val dea-lungul grilei spectrale.&#10;De asemenea, are setări pentru ajustarea înălțimii bărilor spectrale, a vitezei, și a modului în care bările sunt randate (umplere, puncte, contur). Este o vizualizare cu consum redus al procesorului care arată fantastic de bine.</description>
    <description lang="ru">Эта визуализация на основе OpenGL показывает вращающийся трёхмерный анализатор спектра, который движется в такт музыке, создавая эффект волны по всему спектру сетки.⏎&#10;Визуализация имеет настройки для регулировки высоты полос спектра, скорости движения и способа отображения полос (сплошной, точки, каркас), а также обладает небольшим размером и малой нагрузкой на процессор.</description>
    <description lang="sk">Opengl Spectrum je vizualizácia zobrazujúca rotujúci 3D spektrálny analyzátor vykresľovaný pomocou OpenGL, ktorý sa hýbe v rytme hudby a tak vytvára vlny naprieč mriežkou spektra.[CR]&#10;Zároveň má nastavenia upravujúce výšku stĺpcov spektra, ich rýchlosť a ako sú vykresľované (vyplnené, body, drôtový model). Je to jednoduchá vizualizácia s nízkou záťažou CPU, ktorá výborne vyzerá.</description>
    <description lang="sl">OpenGL Spectrum je vizualizacija, ki prikazuje vrtečo 3D spektralno analizato, generirano v OpenGL, ki se premika v ritmu glasbe in ustvarja učinek valovanja v celotnem spektru. Vsebuje tudi nastavitve za prilagoditev višine spektra, hitrosti in oblike (polno, točke, okvir) ter je varčna vizualizacija z nizka porabo CPU-ja, ki izgleda super.</description>
    <description lang="sv">OpenGL-spektrum är en visualisering som visar en roterande 3D-spektrumanalysator renderad i OpenGL. Den rör sig till musikens takt och skapar en vågeffekt över spektrat.&#10;OpenGL-spektrum har inställningar för att justera staplarnas höjd, deras hastighet, hur de ska visas (solida, punkter, ramverk) och är en visualisering med låg cpu-användning samtidigt som den ser bra ut</description>
    <description lang="th">Opengl Spectrum เป็น การแสดงแสงสี ทำให้เห็นการหมุนกราฟวิเคราะห์คลื่นความถี่เสียง แบบ 3 มิติ ที่สร้างขึ้นโดย Opengl ที่ขยับไปตามจังหวะของเพลงที่สร้างผลกระทบเป็นคลื่นไปทั่วตารางความถี่.&#10;นอกจากนี้ยังมีการตั้งค่าเพื่อปรับความสูงของแท่งคลื่นความถี่,ความเร็วและกระบวนการที่แท่งแสดงผล (ของแข็ง, จุด, โครงลวด) ทั้งยังใช้ทรัพยากรน้อยได้ดี, การแสดงแสงสี ที่ใช้ซีพียูต่ำนั่นก็ดูยอดเยี่ยมทีเดียว</description>
    <description lang="uk">OpenGL Spectrum  є візалізаціє що показує обертаючийся 3D спектроаналізатор що промальовується з використанням технології  OpenGL. Спектроаналізатор показує стовпчики змінної висоти що рухаються в такт з музикою і створюють ефект подібний до хвилі.&#10;Ви маєте можливість налаштувати висоту стовпчиків, їх швидкість і те як вони намальовані (Заповнені, контури, крапки). Це досить проста, і невимоглива до процесора візуалізація, але яка має чудовий вигляд.</description>
    <description lang="zh">Opengl Spectrum可视化效果是Opengl渲染的一个旋转的三维频谱分析图像，频谱矩阵随着音乐节拍而象波浪起伏。&#10;你还可以设置频谱棒的高度、变换速度、以及呈现效果（固体、点、框架）。这是一个不错的轻量级，低CPU使用率的可视化效果。</description>
    <description lang="zh_TW">OpenGL Spectrum 是使用 OpenGL 描繪顯示旋轉的3D頻譜分析視覺效果，頻譜格線隨著音樂節拍而像波浪起伏。&#10;它還可以調整頻譜長條的高度、速度以及呈現效果（實心、點狀、線框）。它是個很好的輕量級、低 CPU 使用率的視覺化效果。</description>
    <platform>linux osx ios android</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon
  id="visualization.milkdrop"
  version="1.0.2"
  name="MilkDrop"
  provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <extension
    point="xbmc.player.musicviz"
    library_windx="MilkDrop_win32dx.vis"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af">MilkDrop laat jou sweef deur die klankgolwe wat jy hoor</summary>
    <summary lang="ar">يحلق بك MilkDrop فوق الموجات الصوتية اللتي تسمع</summary>
    <summary lang="be">MilkDrop takes you flying through the soundwaves you're hearing</summary>
    <summary lang="bg">"MilkDrop" ще Ви отведе на пътешествие между звуковите вълни, които чувате</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">MilkDrop et porta volant a través de les ones de so que escoltes</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">MilkDrop s Vámi proletí  skrz zvukové vlny, které slyšíte</summary>
    <summary lang="da">Milkdrop tager dig på en flyvetur gennem lydbølgerne, du lytter til</summary>
    <summary lang="de">MilkDrop nimmt dich mit auf einen Flug durch deine Musik.</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Το MilkDrop σας ταξιδεύει μέσα στα ηχητικά κύματα που ακούτε</summary>
    <summary lang="en">MilkDrop takes you flying through the soundwaves you're hearing</summary>
    <summary lang="es">MilkDrop te lleva volando a través de las ondas que estás escuchando</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">MilkDrop te lleva volando a través de las ondas que estás escuchando</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">MilkDrop the lleva volando a través de las ondas de sonido que estás escuchando</summary>
    <summary lang="et">MilkDrop viib sind lennates läbi helilainete mida kuulad</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">MilkDrop lennättää sinut ääniaaltojen läpi</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">MilkDrop vous fait voyager dans les ondes sonores de votre musique</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">MilkDrop lévate voando a través da ondas de son que esta a ouvir</summary>
    <summary lang="he">MilkDrop לוקח אותך לתעופה דרך גלי הסאונד שאתה שומע</summary>
    <summary lang="hr">MilkDrop vam omogućuje let kroz zvuk koji čujete</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">A Milkdrop végigrepít a zene hullámain</summary>
    <summary lang="is">Með MilkDrop flýgurðu í gegnum hljóðbylgjurnar sem þú heyrir</summary>
    <summary lang="it">MilkDrop ti fa volare tra le onde sonore di ciò che stai ascoltando</summary>
    <summary lang="ja">MilkDrop - 音楽の波の上を飛ぶ</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">MilkDrop은 사운드웨이브 속으로 날아가는듯한 효과를 보여줍니다.</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">MilkDrop nukelia Jus i nuostabu skrydi virs debesu, istiesu fantastisku garsu gausa</summary>
    <summary lang="mk">MilkDrop ве прелетува преку брановите на музиката која ја слушате</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Met MilkDrop vliegt u mee door de soundwaves die je hoort</summary>
    <summary lang="no">MilkDrop tar deg med på en flyreise gjennom lydbølgene du hører</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">MilkDrop zabiera Cię w niesamowity lot w chmurach aktualnie słuchanych dźwięków</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">O MilkDrop leva-o num voo através das ondas sonoras que está a ouvir</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">O MilkDrop leva você para voar nas ondas sonoras que está ouvindo</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">MilkDrop vă face să zburați printre undele audio pe care le auziți</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Milkdrop отправит вас в полёт через звуковые волны, которые вы слышите</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">MilkDrop s Vami poletí zvukovými vlnami, ktoré počúvate</summary>
    <summary lang="sl">MilkDrop vas popelje skozi zvočne valove, ki jih poslušate</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">Milkdrop för dig flygande genom de ljudvågor du hör.</summary>
    <summary lang="uk">MilkDrop забере вас в політ крізь хвилі музики яку ви слухаєте</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">MilkDrop带你与声波一起飞翔</summary>
    <description lang="af">MilkDrop was oorspronklik 'n musiek visualisering "plug-in" vir die Winamp musiek speler. Soos jy na jou musiek luister, laat MilkDrop jou deur die klankgolwe sweef wat jy hoor, en gebruik klop waarnemings om 'n magdom psigedeliese effekte te aktiveer, en 'n visuele reis deur klank te skep.</description>
    <description lang="ar">ميلك دروب كان أصلا عارض موسيقى لمشغل الموسيقى وين امب. عندما تستمع لموسيقاك, كيلك دروب يطير بك خلال موجات صوتية تسمعا حيقيةً, ,و يستخدم كشف الوقع الموسيقي ليؤدي إلى تأثيرات كثيرة, منشئاً رجلة صوت مرئية قيمة.</description>
    <description lang="be">MilkDrop was originally a music visualizer "plug-in" to the Winamp music player. As you listen to your music, MilkDrop takes you flying through the actual soundwaves you're hearing, and uses beat detection to trigger myriad psychedelic effects, creating a rich visual journey through sound.</description>
    <description lang="bg">Първоначално "MilkDrop" е замислена като приставка за музикалния плеър Winamp. Докато слушате музикалната си колекция "MilkDrop" ще Ви накара да "полетите", измежду звуковите вълни, които чувате. Ползва ритъма за да създаде безброй еуфорични ефекти. Така създава едно богато визуално пътешествие в звука.</description>
    <description lang="ca">El MilkDrop era originalment un afegitó de visualització musical pel reproductor Winamp. Mentre escoltes la música MilkDrop et porta volant a través de les ones de so que estàs escoltant al moment, i utilitza detecció de tempo per activar una munió d'efectes psicodèlics i crea un enriquidor viatge visual a través del so.</description>
    <description lang="cs">MikDrop bylo původně vizualizační rozšíření pro přehrávač hudby Winamp. Při poslechu Vaší hudby s Vámi MikDrop prolétá skrze zvukové vlny, které slyšíte a používá detekci taktů, pro spuštění spousty psychedelických efektů, vytvářejíce tak zajímavou vizuální cestu skrze zvuk.</description>
    <description lang="da">Milkdrop var oprindeligt et musikvisualisering "plug-in" til Winamp musikafspilleren. Mens du lytter til din musik, tager Milkdrop dig på en flyvetur gennem de faktiske lydbølger du hører og bruger beat-genkendelse til at udløse en myriade af psykedeliske effekter, der skaber en visuel rejse gennem lyd.</description>
    <description lang="de">MilkDrop war ursprünglich ein Musik-Visualizer "Plug-in" für den Musik-Player Winamp.Wenn Sie Ihre Musik hören, fliegen Sie mit MilkDrop durch die aktuellen Klangwellen die Sie hören. Und die Beat-Erkennung wird genutzt um unzählige psychedelische Effekte auslösen, die Schaffung einer visuellen Reise durch den Klang.</description>
    <description lang="el">Το MilkDrop ήταν αρχικά ένα "plug-in" μουσικών οπτικοποιήσεων του Winamp. Καθώς παίζετε τη μουσική σας, το MilkDrop σας ταξιδεύει μέσα στα πραγματικά ηχητικά κύματα που ακούτε, και χρησιμοποιεί ανίχνευση ρυθμού για να ενεργοποιήσει ένα πλήθος ψυχεδελικών εφέ, δημιουργώντας ένα πλούσιο οπτικό ταξίδι μέσα στον ήχο.</description>
    <description lang="en">MilkDrop was originally a music visualizer "plug-in" to the Winamp music player. As you listen to your music, MilkDrop takes you flying through the actual soundwaves you're hearing, and uses beat detection to trigger myriad psychedelic effects, creating a rich visual journey through sound.</description>
    <description lang="es">MilkDrop era originalmente un plug-in visualizador de música para Winamp. Mientras escuchas música, MilkDrop te lleva volando a través de las ondas que estás escuchando, y utiliza la detección del ritmo para activar una gran cantidad de efectos psicodélicos, creando una rica experiencia visual a través del sonido.</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">MilkDrop era originalmente un plug-in visualizador de música para Winamp. Mientras escuchas música, MilkDrop te lleva volando a través de las ondas que estás escuchando, y utiliza la detección del ritmo para activar una gran cantidad de efectos psicodélicos, creando una rica experiencia visual a través del sonido.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">MilkDrop originalmente fue un "plug-in" visualizador de música para el reproductor de música Winamp. Mientras escuchas tu músuca, MilkDrop te lleva volando a través de las ondas de sonido que estás escuchando en ese momento, y usa detección de ritmo para desencadenar múltiples efectos psicodélicos, creando un rico recorrido visual a través del sonido.</description>
    <description lang="et">MilkDrop oli algselt muusika visuaal plugin Winamp'ile. Muusikat kuulates viib MilkDrop sind lennates läbi reaalsete helilainete mida kuulad. MilkDrop kasutab rütmituvastust, et päästa valla tohutu hulk psühhedeelseid efekte luues visuaalidest rikka teekonna läbi heli.</description>
    <description lang="fi">MilkDrop oli alunperin Winampin visualisaattorilisäosa. Kuunnellessasi musiikkia MilkDrop lennättää sinut kuulemiesi ääniaaltojen läpi ja käyttää tahdintunnistusta lukemattomien psykedeelisten tehosteiden toistamiseen, luoden visuaalisen matkan musiikin läpi.</description>
    <description lang="fr">MilkDrop était à l'origine une extension de visualisation musicale pour le lecteur audio Winamp. Pendant que vous écoutez votre musique, Milkdrop vous fait voyager à travers les ondes sonores que vous entendez, détectant le rythme pour déclencher une myriade d'effets psychédéliques, créant ainsi une riche expérience visuelle et sonore.</description>
    <description lang="gl">MilkDrop foi orixinalmente un plugin de Visualización para múica do reprodutor de música Winamp. Nametres vostede escoita a súa música, MilkDrop lévao voando a través das ondas de son que esta a ouvir, e emprega a detección de ritmo para activar milleiros de efectos psicodélicos, creando unha rica viaxe visual a través do son.</description>
    <description lang="he">MilkDrop was originally a music visualizer "plug-in" to the Winamp music player. As you listen to your music, MilkDrop takes you flying through the actual soundwaves you're hearing, and uses beat detection to trigger myriad psychedelic effects, creating a rich visual journey through sound.</description>
    <description lang="hr">MilkDrop je orginalno bio zamišljen kao "dodatak", glazbeni vizualizator Winamp glazbenog programa. Dok slušate vašu glazbu, MilkDrop vam omogućuje let kroz zvuk koji čujete i koristi otkrivanje taktova da pokrenuo bezbroj psihodelični efekata, tako stvarajući visualno bogato putovanje kroz zvuk.</description>
    <description lang="hu">A Milkdrop eredetileg egy beépülőmodul volt a Winamp zenelejátszóhoz. Ahogy hallgatod a zenét, a Milkdrop keresztülrepít a hallható hanghullámokon, felhasználva a dobritmust pszihedelikus effektusok létrehozására gazdag látványvilág megteremtésével.</description>
    <description lang="is">Milkdrop var upprunalega viðbót við Winamp tónlistarspilarann. Þegar þú hlustar á tónlistina, fer Milkdrop með þig á flug í gegnum hljóðbylgjurnar sem þú heyrir og notar taktskynjun til að setja af stað allskonar effekta sem skapa myndrænt ferðalag í gegnum tónlistarupplifunina</description>
    <description lang="it">MilkDrop era, in origine, un "plug-in" di visualizzazione per Winamp. Mentre ascolti la musica, MilkDrop ti fa volare tra le onde sonore di ciò che stai ascoltando usando la rilevazione del ritmo per sincronizzare una miriade di effetti psichedelici, creando un ricco viaggio visuale attraverso il suono.</description>
    <description lang="ja">MilkDrop は元々 Winamp 音楽プレーヤーのビジュアライザープラグインでした。音楽を再生すると、音楽にあわせた波の上を飛んでいるような視覚効果が現れ、ビート検出により無数のサイケデリックな効果が生まれ、音による視覚的体験を生み出します。</description>
    <description lang="ko">MilkDrop는 원래 윈앰프의 음악 시각화 플러그인입니다. 음악을 들으면서 사운드 웨이브로 날아가는듯한 효과를 보여주며 비트 감지를 해서 다양한 싸이키데릭한 효과를 만들어 풍부한 시각적 경험을 하게합니다.</description>
    <description lang="lt">MilkDrop vizualizacija, gauta is Winamp. Klausantis muzikos, MilkDrop nukelia jus i nuostabu skrydi virs debesu, naudojamas ritmo aptikimas, kuris sinchronizuoja muzikos vaizdo efektus.</description>
    <description lang="mk">MilkDrop беше визуализација допонување на Winamp music player. Како што ја слушате музиката, MilkDrop ве прелетува преку актуелните музички бранови, и користи детекција на битот за да покрене myriad психоделични ефекти, креирајќи богато визуелно патување низ звукот.</description>
    <description lang="nl">Milkdrop was oorspronkelijk een muziekvisualisatieplug-in voor de Winamp-muziekspeler. Terwijl u uw muziek beluistert vliegt Milkdrop u door de soundwaves die u op dat moment hoort. Op basis van de beat produceert het een veelvoud aan psychedelische effecten.</description>
    <description lang="no">MilkDrop var orginalt en musikk visualiserings "plug-in" til Winamp musikk spiller. Mens du lytter til musikk, tar MilkDrop deg med på en flytur gjennom de faktiske lydbølgene du hører og bruker (beat detection) for å skape en hau med psykadeliske effekter som skaper en rik visuell ferd gjennom lyd.</description>
    <description lang="pl">MilkDrop jest wizualizacją pochodzącą z odtwarzacza Winamp. W czasie słuchania muzyki, MilkDrop zabiera użytkownika w niesamowity lot pomiędzy aktualnie odtwarzanymi falami dźwiękowymi, używając detekcji beatu, która synchronizuje efekty wizualne z muzyką.</description>
    <description lang="pt">Originalmente, o MilkDrop era uma visualização do leitor de música Winamp. Ao ouvir a sua música, o MilkDrop leva-o a voar pelas ondas sonoras que está a ouvir, detectando o ritmo da música e desencadeando uma variedade de efeitos psicadélicos. Cria, assim, uma viagem inesquecível pelo som.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">MilkDrop era originalmente uma visualização do reprodutor de música Winamp. Ao ouvir a sua música, o MilkDrop leva-o a voar nas ondas sonoras que está a ouvir, usando detecção de batida para desencadear uma miríade de efeitos psicodélicos. Cria, assim, uma viagem visual inesquecível pelo som.</description>
    <description lang="ro">MilkDrop a fost original un „modul” de vizualizare pentru lectorul de muzică Winamp. În timp ce ascultați muzica, MilkDrop vă face să zburați printre undele audio actuale pe care le auziți și folosește detecția bătăii pentru a activa miriada de efecte psihedelice, creând o călătorie vizuală bogată printre sunete.</description>
    <description lang="ru">MilkDrop изначально был модулем визуализации музыки для проигрывателя Winamp. Когда вы слушаете музыку, MilkDrop создает визуальное ощущение полёта по звуковым волнам, а также использует обнаружение ритма для активации множества психоделических эффектов.</description>
    <description lang="sk">MilkDrop bol pôvodne hudobným vizualizačným rozšírením Winamp prehrávača. Pri počúvaní hudby s Vami MilkDrop letí zvukovými vlnami, ktoré počúvate a použitím detekcie rytmu spúšťa nespočetné psychodelické efekty, a vytvára bohatú vizuálnu cestu zvukom.</description>
    <description lang="sl">MilkDrop je bila prvotno vizualizacija za predvajalnik Winamp. Ko poslušate vašo glasbo, vas MilkDrop popelje skozi dejansko valovanje, ki ga slišite, in uporablja zaznavanje ritma, kar omogoči psihedelični efekt in bogato vizualno izkušnjo predvajanja glasbe.</description>
    <description lang="sv">Milkdrop var ursprungligen ett visualiserarande ljudplug-in till Winamp. Medan du lyssnar på din musik så för dig Milkdrop flygande genom de ljudvågor du hör och använder rytmavkänning för att ge dig psykedeliska effekter som skapar en mäktig visuell resa via ljudet.</description>
    <description lang="zh">MilkDrop是来自于Winamp音乐播放器的可视化插件。在你听音乐时，MilkDrop通过节拍检测触发的无数迷幻的效果，带你与声波一起飞翔，给你带来丰富的音乐和视觉旅程。</description>
    <platform>windx</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon
  id="visualization.projectm"
  version="1.0.3"
  name="projectM"
  provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <extension
    point="xbmc.player.musicviz"
    library_linux="projectM.vis"
    library_wingl="projectM_win32.vis"
    library_osx="projectM.vis">
    <settings>
      <userdirs>
        <userdir path="special://profile/addon_data/visualization.projectm"/>
      </userdirs>
    </settings>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af">projectM vat jou op 'n vlug deur die klankgolwe wat jy hoor</summary>
    <summary lang="ar">مشروع M يجعلك تطير بين موحات الصوت التي تسمعها</summary>
    <summary lang="be">projectM takes you flying through the soundwaves you're hearing</summary>
    <summary lang="bg">"projectM" ще Ви отведе на пътешествие между звуковите вълни, които чувате</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">projectM et porta volant a través de les ones que escoltes</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">projectM s Vámi proletí zvukovými vlnamy, které posloucháte</summary>
    <summary lang="da">projectM tager dig på en flyvetur gennem lydbølgerne, du lytter til</summary>
    <summary lang="de">projectM lässt euch durch den Sound fliegen, den Ihr gerade hört</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Το projectM σας ταξιδεύει μέσα στα ηχητικά κύματα που ακούτε</summary>
    <summary lang="en">projectM takes you flying through the soundwaves you're hearing</summary>
    <summary lang="es">projectM te lleva volando a través de las ondas que estás escuchando</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">projectM te lleva volando a través de las ondas que estás escuchando</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">projectM te lleva volando a través de las ondas de sonido que estás escuchando</summary>
    <summary lang="et">projectM viib sind lennates läbi helilainete mida kuulad</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">projectM lennättää sinut ääniaaltojen läpi</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">projectM vous entraine à travers les ondes sonores que vous écoutez</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">projectM lévao voando a través das ondas de son que está a ouvir</summary>
    <summary lang="he">projectM לוקח אותך לתעופה דרך גלי הסאונד שאתה שומע</summary>
    <summary lang="hr">projectM vam omogućuje let kroz zvuk koji čujete</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">A projectM végigrepít a zene hullámain</summary>
    <summary lang="is">Með projectM flýgurðu í gegnum hljóðbylgjurnar sem þú heyrir</summary>
    <summary lang="it">projectM ti fa volare tra le onde sonore di ciò che stai ascoltando</summary>
    <summary lang="ja">projectM - 音楽の波の上を飛ぶ</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">projectM 은 사운드웨이브 속으로 날아가는듯한 효과를 보여줍니다.</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">projectM nukelia Jus į nuostabų skrydį virš debesų, ištiesų fantastiškų garsų gausą</summary>
    <summary lang="mk">projectM ве води на летање низ звучните бранови на музиката што ја слушате</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">projectM-visualisatie</summary>
    <summary lang="no">projectM tar deg på en reise flygende gjenom lydbølgene du hører</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">projectM zabiera Cię w niesamowity lot w chmurach aktualnie słuchanych dźwięków</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">O projectM leva-o num voo através das ondas sonoras que está a ouvir</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">O projectM leva-o a voar nas ondas sonoras que está a ouvir</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">projectM îți oferă o senzație auditivă unică astfel încât simți că zbori printre undele sonore pe care le asculți</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">projectM отправит вас в полёт через звуковые волны, которые вы слышите</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">projektM s Vami poletí zvukovými vlnami, ktoré počúvate</summary>
    <summary lang="sl">projectM vas popelje čez valovanje zvoka, kot ga slišite</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">projectM tar med dig på en flygtur genom ljudvågorna du hör</summary>
    <summary lang="uk">projectM забирає вас в політ крізь хвилі музики яку ви слухаєте</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">projectM带你与声波一起飞翔</summary>
    <description lang="af">projectM is 'n ontsagwekkende musiek visualiseerder. Daar is niks beter in die wêreld van Unix nie. projectM se grootheid kom van die harde werk van die gemeenskap. Gebruikers soos jy kan voorafinstellings skep wat musiek met ongelooflike visualiserings konnekteer. Probeer dit!&#10;projectM Visualisering is 'n geLGPL'de herimplementasie van Milkdrop onder OpenGL&#10;Al wat projectM benodig is 'n video kaart met 3D versnelling en jou gunsteling musiek.</description>
    <description lang="ar">مشروع M هو مصورللموسقى رائع. لا شي في العالم أفضل من Unix. عظمة مشروع M تأتي من عمل المجتمع الجاد. يستطيع مستخدمون مثلك إنشاء مسبقات تتصل بالموسقى لصور رائعة. جربه&#10;تصوير مشروع M &#10;كل ما يتطلبه مشروع M هو كرت شاشة بتسارع 3D و موسيقاك المفضلة.</description>
    <description lang="be">projectM is an awesome music visualizer. There is nothing better in the world of Unix. projectM's greatness comes from the hard work of the community. Users like you can create presets that connect music with incredible visuals. Try it!&#10;projectM Visualization is an LGPL'ed reimplementation of Milkdrop under OpenGL&#10;All projectM requires is a video card with 3D acceleration and your favorite music.</description>
    <description lang="bg">"projectM" е страхотна визуализация, плод на упорит труд от страна на общността. В света на Unix не съществува нищо по-добро. Потребители, като Вас, създават предварително комбинации от настройки, които се ползват като модел за визуализацията и така свързват звука с невероятни визуални ефекти. Пробвайте!&#10;Визуализацията "projectM" е преработка на Milkdrop под лиценза LGPL, основана на OpenGL.&#10;"projectM" изисква видео карта с 3D ускорение и любимата Ви музика.</description>
    <description lang="ca">El projectM és un visualitzador de música impressionant. No hi ha res millor al món Unix. La grandesa de projectM prové del dur treball de la comunitat. Els usuaris com tu poden crear predefinits que connecten la música amb visualitzacions increibles. Prova-ho!&#10;La Visualització projectM és una re-implementació en LGPL de Milkdrop baix OpenGL&#10;Tot el que projectM requereix és una tarja amb acceleració 3D i la teva música preferida.</description>
    <description lang="cs">projectM je úžasný hudební vizualizér. Ve světě Unixu neexistuje nic lepšího. Velikost projectuM pochází z tvrdé práce komunity. Uživatelé, jako jste vy, mohou vytvářet předvolby, které spojují hudbu s fantastickými vizuálními zážitky. Zkuste to!&#10;projectM vizualizace je LGPL reimplementace Milkdropu pod OpenGL.&#10;Vše co projectM vyžaduje je grafická karta s 3D akcelerací a Vaše oblíbená hudba.</description>
    <description lang="da">projectM er en fantastisk musikvisualisering. Der findes intet bedre i Unix-verdenen. projectMs storhed kommer fra brugerbasens hårde arbejde. Brugere, som dig selv, kan skabe forudindstillinger, som forbinder musik med utrolige visualiseringer. Prøv det!&#10;projectM Visualization er en LGPLed reimplementation af Milkdrop under OpenGL.&#10;Alt hvad projectM kræver er et grafikkort med 3D-acceleration og din yndlingsmusik.</description>
    <description lang="de">projectM ist eine unglaublicher Musik-Visualisierung. In der Unix-Welt gibt es nichts besseres. Die Einzigartigkeit kommt durch die harte Arbeit der Community. User wie du können "Presets" schreiben, welche sich mit der Musik verbinden. Versuche es selber!&#10;projectM ist die LGPL Reimplementierung von Milkdrop als OpenGL Variante&#10;Alles was prjectM benötigt ist eine Grafikkarte mit 3D Beschleunigung und deine Lieblingmusik</description>
    <description lang="el">Το projectM είναι ένας φοβερός μουσικός οπτικοποιητής. Δεν υπάρχει τίποτα καλύτερο στον κόσμο του Unix. Το μεγαλείο του projectM πηγάζει από τη σκληρή δουλειά της κοινότητας. Χρήστες όπως εσείς μπορούν να δημιουργήσουν προρυθμίσεις συνδέοντας τη μουσική με απίστευτες απεικονίσεις. Δοκιμάστε το!&#10;Η Οπτικοποίηση projectM αποτελεί μία νέα LGPL υλοποίηση του Milkdrop υπό το OpenGL&#10;Το μόνο που απαιτείται από το projectM είναι μία κάρτα γραφικών με τρισδιάστατη (3D) επιτάχυνση, και την αγαπημένη σας μουσική.</description>
    <description lang="en">projectM is an awesome music visualizer. There is nothing better in the world of Unix. projectM's greatness comes from the hard work of the community. Users like you can create presets that connect music with incredible visuals. Try it!&#10;projectM Visualization is an LGPL'ed reimplementation of Milkdrop under OpenGL&#10;All projectM requires is a video card with 3D acceleration and your favorite music.</description>
    <description lang="es">projectM es un fantástico visualizador de música. No hay nada mejor en el universo Unix. La grandeza de projectM proviene del duro trabajo de la comunidad. Usuarios como usted pueden crear ajustes preestablecidos que conecten la música con visualizaciones increibles. ¡Pruébelo!&#10;projectM Visualization es una reimplantación de Milkdrop bajo licencia LGPL y renderizado en OpenGL.&#10;Todo lo que projectM necesita es una tarjeta de vídeo con aceleración 3D y su música favorita.</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">projectM es un fantástico visualizador de música. No hay nada mejor en el universo Unix. La grandeza de projectM proviene del duro trabajo de la comunidad. Usuarios como tu pueden crear ajustes preestablecidos que conecten la música con visualizaciones increíbles. ¡Pruebalo!&#10;projectM Visualization es una reimplantación de Milkdrop bajo licencia LGPL y renderizado en OpenGL.&#10;Todo lo que projectM necesita es una tarjeta de video con aceleración 3D y tu música favorita.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">projectM es un visualizador de música sorprendente. No hay nada mejor en el mundo de Unix. La grandeza de projectM proviene del duro trabajo de la comunidad. Usuarios como tú pueden crear preaujstes que conectan la música con increíbles imágenes. Inténtalo!&#10;La visualización projectM es una reimplementación en LGPL de Milkdrop bajo OpenGL.&#10;Todo lo que projectM necesita es una tarjeta de video con aceleración 3D y tu música favorita.</description>
    <description lang="et">projectM on äge muusika visuaal. Unixi maailmas pole midagi paremat. projectM'i suurus on saavutatud kogukonna ühise raske töö tulemusena. Kasutajad nagu sina saavad luua eelseadeid, mis ühendavad muusika imeliste visualidega. Proovi seda! projectM visualiseerimine on litsentseeritud (LGPL) uuskasutus Milkdrop'ist OpenGL keskkonnas.&#10;Ainus mida projectM vajab, on 3D kiirendusega videokaart ja sinu lemmikmuusika.</description>
    <description lang="fi">projectM on uskomaton musiikkivisualisointi, joka on yhteisön kovan työn tulos. Käyttäjät voivat luoda esiasetuksia, jotka yhdistävät musiikin kuviin.&#10;projectM -visualisointi on LGPL-lisensoitu Milkdropin uudelleenimplementointi OpenGL:llä.&#10;projectM tarvitsee vain 3D-kiihdyttävän näytönohjaimen ja lempimusiikkisi.</description>
    <description lang="fr">projectM est un fantastique visualiseur musical. Il n'y a rien de mieux dans l'univers Unix. L'ampleur de projectM vient du travail énorme de la communauté. Des utilisateurs comme vous peuvent créer des préréglages qui connecteront la musique avec des visuels incroyables. Essayez-le!&#10;La visualisation projectM est une réalisation sous LGPL de Milkdrop en OpenGL.&#10;Le seul pré-requis pour projectM est une carte graphique avec accélération 3D et votre musique favorite.</description>
    <description lang="gl">projectM é unha impresionante Visualización de música. Non hai nada mellor no mundo Unix.  A grandeza de projectM ven da dura xeira da comunidade. Usuarios coma vostede poden crear preconfiguracións que conectan a música con incribles visualizacións. Próbeo!&#10;A Visualización projectM é unha reimplementación de Milkdrop empregando OpenGL e con licencia LGPL.&#10;Todo o que precisa projectM é unha tarxeta gráfica con aceleración 3D e a súa música favorita.</description>
    <description lang="he">projectM is an awesome music visualizer. There is nothing better in the world of Unix. projectM's greatness comes from the hard work of the community. Users like you can create presets that connect music with incredible visuals. Try it!&#10;projectM Visualization is an LGPL'ed reimplementation of Milkdrop under OpenGL&#10;All projectM requires is a video card with 3D acceleration and your favorite music.</description>
    <description lang="hr">projectM je fenomenalan glazbeni visualizer. Ne postoji ništa bolje u svijetu Unix-a. Veličina projectM-a dolazi zbog predanosti njegove zajednice. Korisnici kao što ste vi, mogu stvoriti zadane postavke koje povezuju muziku i nevjerovatne vizuale. Isprobajte! projectM Vizualizacija je LGPL reimplementacija Milkdrop-a pod OpenGL&#10;Sve što projectM zahtjeva je video kartica sa 3d ubrzanjem i vašu omiljenu glazbu.</description>
    <description lang="hu">A projectM egy fantasztikus zenei vizualizáció. Nincs ennél jobb a Unix világban. A projectM különlegessége, hogy egy egész fejlesztői közösség nehéz munkájából jött létre. A felhasználók, mint te egyedi beállításokat hozhatnak létre ami összekapcsolja a zenét a hihetetlen látványelemekkel. Próbáld ki!&#10;A projectM Vizualizáció a Milkdrop újrakódolása LGPL licenc alatt, OpenGL videókártya támogatást használva.&#10;Minden projectM látványbeállításhoz 3D gyorsításra képes videókártya és a kedvenc zenéd szükséges.</description>
    <description lang="is">projectM er frábær myndskreyting. það er ekkert betra í Unix heiminum. Gæði projectM koma til vegna framlags samfélagsins.Notendur eins og þú geta búið til forstillingar sem tengja tónlist við ótrúlega myndræna upplifun. Prófaðu!⏎ projectM myndskreyting er LGPL útgáfa af Milkdrop með OpenGL⏎ Allt sem projectM þarfnast er skjákort með þrívíddar hraðli  3D og uppáhalds tónlistin þín.</description>
    <description lang="it">projectM è un incredibile visualizzazione musicale. E' il meglio del mondo Unix. La grandezza di projectM proviene dal duro lavoro della comunità. Gli utenti come te possono creare preset che connetto la musica con incredibili grafiche. Provalo!&#10;projectM è una reimplementazione LGPL di Milkdrop sotto OpenGL&#10;Tutti i projectM richiedono una scheda video con accelerazione 3D e la tua musica preferita.</description>
    <description lang="ja">projectM is an awesome music visualizer. There is nothing better in the world of Unix. projectM's greatness comes from the hard work of the community. Users like you can create presets that connect music with incredible visuals. Try it!&#10;projectM Visualization is an LGPL'ed reimplementation of Milkdrop under OpenGL&#10;All projectM requires is a video card with 3D acceleration and your favorite music.</description>
    <description lang="ko">projectM은 멋진 음악 시각화입니다. Unix에는 이것보다 좋은것은 없습니다. projectM은 많은 사람들에 의해 개발되었습니다. 여러분과 같은 유저들이 음악을 표현하는 프리셋을 만들었습니다. projectM 음악시각화는 OpenGL에서 작동하도록 Milkdrop를 새로 만든것입니다. 모든 projectM은 3D 가속이 되는 비디오카드와 음악이 필요합니다.</description>
    <description lang="lt">ProjectM yra išskirtinė muzikos vizualizacija. Nėra nieko geriau, Unix pasaulyje. ProjectM spindesys tai sunkus darbas bendruomenėje. Naudotojai, tokie kaip Jūs galite sukurti ir suderinti muziką su puikiais vizualizacijos  efektais. Sužinokite!&#10;ProjectM yra įgyvendinimas iš Milkdrop pagal LGPL licenciją, ir naudoja OpenGL&#10;Viskas ko reikia projectM tai vaizdo plokštės su 3D akceleracija (greitėjimu) ir geros muzikos.</description>
    <description lang="mk">projectM is an awesome music visualizer. There is nothing better in the world of Unix. projectM's greatness comes from the hard work of the community. Users like you can create presets that connect music with incredible visuals. Try it!⏎ projectM Visualization is an LGPL'ed reimplementation of Milkdrop under OpenGL⏎ All projectM requires is a video card with 3D acceleration and your favorite music.</description>
    <description lang="nl">ProjectM is een geweldige muziekvisualisatie. Er bestaat niets beters in de UNIX-wereld. Het success van ProjectM is het resultaat van het harde werk van de XBMC-gemeenschap. U kunt hun eigen presets instellen die muziek linken aan verbluffende visualisaties. Probeer het uit!&#10;ProjectM-visualisatie is beschikbaar onder de LGPL-licentie en is een herimplementatie van Milkdrop (OpenGL). Alles wat projectM vereist is een videokaart met 3D-versnelling en jouw favoriete muziek.</description>
    <description lang="no">projectM er en awesome musikk visualisering. Der er ingenting bedre i Unix verden. projectM er så flott takket være et hardt arbeidende felleskap. Brukere som deg kan lage forhåndsinnstillinger som kobler musikk med utrolige visualiseringer. Prøv det!&#10;projectM visualiseringen er en LGPL reinplimentasjon av Milkdrop under OpenGL&#10;Alt projectM trenger er et grafikkort med 3D støtte og din favoritt musikk</description>
    <description lang="pl">projectM to rewelacyjna wizualizacją muzyki. Nie ma nic lepszego w świecie Unixa. Wspaniałość projectM wywodzi się ciężkiej pracy społeczności. Użytkownicy tacy jak Ty, mogą tworzyć efekty łączące muzykę z niesamowitymi efektami wizualnymi. Przekonaj się!&#10;projectM jest reimplementacją Milkdropa na licencji LGPL i używa OpenGL&#10;Wszystko czego wymaga projectM, to karta graficzna wspierająca akcelerację 3D oraz zasoby Twojej muzyki.</description>
    <description lang="pt">O projectM é uma fantástica visualização de música. Não há melhor no mundo Unix. A grandeza do projectM advém do trabalho árduo da comunidade. Qualquer utilizador pode criar pré-selecções que combinam a música com visualizações incríveis. Experimente!&#10;O visualizador projectM é uma reimplementação do Milkdrop OpenGL sob uma licença LGPL. Tudo o que o projectM precisa é de uma placa gráfica com aceleração 3D e a sua música favorita.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">O projectM é um fantástico visualizador de música. Não existe nenhum melhor no mundo Unix. A grandeza do projectM advém do trabalho árduo da comunidade. Utilizadores como você podem criar pré-definições que ligam a música a visualizações incríveis. Experimente!&#10;O visualizador projectM é uma reimplementação do Milkdrop OpenGL sob uma licença LGPL. Tudo o que o projectM necessita é de uma placa gráfica com aceleração 3D e a sua música favorita.</description>
    <description lang="ro">projectM este un plugin uimitor. Nu există nimic mai bun în lumea Unix. Măreția projectM vine din munca întregii comunități. Utilizatori ca și tine pot crea presetări care conectează muzica cu vizualizări incredibile. Încearcă și tu!&#10;Vizualizarea projectM este o reimplementare LGPL a lui Milkdrop sub OpenGL.&#10;Tot ceea ce necesită projectM este o placă video cu accelerare 3D și muzica ta favorită.</description>
    <description lang="ru">projectM удивительным образом визуализирует музыку. В мире Unix нет ничего лучше. projectM является результатом напряжённой работы сообщества. Пользователи могут создавать наборы настроек, которые объединяют музыку и невероятные визуальные эффекты. Попробуйте сами!⏎&#10;Визуализация projectM представляет собой LGPL-реализацию Milkdrop на основе OpenGL⏎&#10;Всё, что требуется для визуализации — это видеокарта с 3D-ускорением и любимая музыка.</description>
    <description lang="sk">projektM je úžasný hudobný vizualizér. Vo svete Unixu neexistuje nič lepšie. Veľkosť projectM pramení z tvrdej práce komunity. Užívatelia ako ty vytvárajú Predvoľby, ktoré spájajú hudbu s fantastickými vizualizáciami. Vyskúšaj to![CR] projectM vizualizácie sú LGPL implementáciou vizualizácií Milkdrop s použitím OpenGL.[CR] Jediné čo projectM potrebuje je grafickú kartu s 3D akceleráciou a Vašu obľúbenú hudbu.</description>
    <description lang="sl">projectM je glasbeni vizualizator. Nič ni boljšega v svetu Unixa. Veličina ProjectM izhaja iz garanja skupnosti. Uporabniki, kot vi, si lahko ustvarite prednastavitve, ki povezujejo glasbo z neverjetno vizualizacijo. Poskusite!&#10;projectM Vizualizacija je LGPL reimplementacija Milkdropa v okviru OpenGL.&#10;projectM potrebuje le grafično kartico s 3D pospeševanjem in vašo najljubšo glasbo.</description>
    <description lang="sv">projectM är en fantastisk musikvisualisering. Det finns inget bättre i Unixvärlden. projectM's storhet kommer från gemenskapens hårda jobb. Användare som du kan skapa förval som förenar musiken med otroliga visualiseringar. Prova det!&#10;projectM visualisering är en LGPL-implementation av Milkdrop i OpenGL&#10;Alla projectM kräver ett grafikkort med 3D-acceleration och din favoritmusik.</description>
    <description lang="zh">projectM是一个音乐可视化效果。它是Unix世界中最好的。它的伟大来自于社区的辛苦工作。使用者可以创建预设参数把音乐和难以置信的可视化效果连接起来。试试吧！&#10;projectM可视化效果是用OpenGL按照LGPL协议对Milkdrop的重新实现&#10;projectM所要求的仅是一块有3D加速功能的显卡和你喜爱的音乐。</description>
    <platform>linux osx wingl</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon
  id="visualization.waveform"
  version="1.0.2"
  name="Waveform"
  provider-name="MrC">
  <extension
    point="xbmc.player.musicviz"
    library_linux="Waveform.vis"
    library_windx="Waveform_win32.vis"
    library_osx="Waveform.vis"
    library_android="libvisWaveform.so"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af">Visualisering wat 2 golfvorm grafieke op die skerm vertoon</summary>
    <summary lang="ar">التصوير يظهر2 رسم بياني موجي على الشاشة</summary>
    <summary lang="be">Візуалізацыя што паказвае 2 графікі сыгналу на экране</summary>
    <summary lang="bg">Визуализация представяща две осцилиращи вълни</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">Visualització que mostra 2 gràfics en forma d'ona a la pantalla</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">Vizualizace zobrazující 2 grafy průběhu vlny na obrazovce</summary>
    <summary lang="da">Visualisering der viser 2 bølgeagtige grafer på skærmen</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Eine Visualisierung, welche 2 wellenförmige Grafiken auf dem Bildschirm zeigt</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Οπτικοποίηση που εμφανίζει 2 Κυματομορφές στην οθόνη</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Visualization showing 2 Waveform Graphs on the screen</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Visualización mostrando 2 gráficos de ondas en la pantalla</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Visualización mostrando 2 gráficos de ondas en la pantalla</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Visualización que muestra 2 Gráficos de Forma de onda</summary>
    <summary lang="et">Visuaal, mis näitab ekraanil kahte signaalikujulist graafikut</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">Kaksi aaltomuotograafia</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Visualisation affichant 2 graphiques de forme d'onde à l'écran</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">Visualización amosando 2 gráficos en forma de onde na pantalla</summary>
    <summary lang="he">חיזוי אשר מציג 2 גרפיים בצורת גל על המסך</summary>
    <summary lang="hr">Vizualizacija koja prikazuje 2 waveform grafikona.</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Vizualizáció két hullámformával</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Visualizzatore che mostra 2 grafici di forma d'onda sullo schermo</summary>
    <summary lang="ja">画面に2波形グラフを表示するビジュアライザー</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">두개의 웨이브폼을 보여주는 음악시각화</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">Vizualizacija kuri parodo dvi garso bangas</summary>
    <summary lang="mk">Визуализација која покажува 2 брана на екранот</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Visualisatie die twee grafieken in golfvorm weergeeft</summary>
    <summary lang="no">Visualisator som viser to bølgeformede grafer på skjermen</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Wizualizacja pokazująca dwie fale dźwięku</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Visualização que mostra 2 gráficos ondulantes no ecrã</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Visualização que mostra 2 gráficos ondulantes</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Vizualizare care arată 2 grafice Waveform pe ecran</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Визуализация, показывающая  на экране 2 волновых графика</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Visualisering som visar 2 vågformsgrafer på skärmen</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">Vizualizácia zobrazujúca 2 grafy priebehu signálu</summary>
    <summary lang="sl">Vizualizacija zvoka z dvema valovnima oblikama</summary>
    <summary lang="sq">Vizualizim që shfaq 2 Grafikë Valëzues në ekran</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">Visualisering som visar 2 vågformgrafer på skärmen</summary>
    <summary lang="th">กำลังแสดงผลภาพเวอร์ชวลไลเซชั่น 'Waveform' เป็น 2  กราฟสัญญาณบนหน้าจอ</summary>
    <summary lang="uk">Візуалізація показує на екрані 2 лінії, що змінюються в такт з музикою.</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">在屏幕上显示两个波形图的可视化效果</summary>
    <description lang="af">Golfvorm is 'n eenvoudige visualisering wat 2 golfvorm grafieke op die skerm vertoon, een elk vir Linker en Regter kanale wat beweeg op die maat van die musiek.</description>
    <description lang="ar">التشكيل الموجي هو تصوير بسيط يظهر2 رسم بياني موجي على الشاشة, واحد لقنوات اليسار و اليمين التر تتحرك على وقع الموسيقى</description>
    <description lang="be">Waveform is a simple Visualization showing 2 Waveform Graphs on the screen, One each for Left and Right channels that move to the beat of the music</description>
    <description lang="bg">Waveform представя графика на две осцилиращи вълни на екрана, по една за всеки канал (ляв и десен), който реагират на ритъма на музиката.</description>
    <description lang="ca">Waveform és una visualització molt simple que mostra 2 gràfics en forma d'ona a la pantalla, un per a cada un dels canals, esquerre i dret, que es mouen al ritme de la música.</description>
    <description lang="cs">Průběh vlny je jednoduchá vizualizace zobrazující 2 grafy průběhu vlny na obrazovce, které znázorňují levý a pravý kanál a pohybují se v rytmu hudby</description>
    <description lang="da">Waveform er en simpel visualisering, der viser 2 bølgeagtige grafer på skærmen. Én til den venstre og én til den højre kanal, der bevæger sig til musikkens rytme.</description>
    <description lang="de">Waveform  ist eine einfache Visualisierung, welche 2 wellenförmige Grafiken zeigt. Je eine Grafik für den linken und rechten Kanal, welche sich im Takt der Musik bewegen</description>
    <description lang="el">Το Waveform είναι μία απλή Οπτικοποίηση του εμφανίζει 2 Κυματομορφές στην οθόνη, μία για το Αριστερό και μία για το Δεξί κανάλι οι οποίες κινούνται στο ρυθμό της μουσικής</description>
    <description lang="en">Waveform is a simple Visualization showing 2 Waveform Graphs on the screen, One each for Left and Right channels that move to the beat of the music</description>
    <description lang="es">Waveform es un sencillo visualizador que muestra 2 gráficos de ondas en la pantalla, uno para cada canal, derecho e izquierdo, que se mueven al ritmo de la música.</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">Waveform es un sencillo visualizador que muestra 2 gráficos de ondas en la pantalla, uno para cada canal, derecho e izquierdo, que se mueven al ritmo de la música.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">Waveform es una Visualización simple que muestra 2 Gráficos de Forma de onda en la pantalla, uno para cada canal Izquierdo y Derecho que se mueven al ritmo de la música</description>
    <description lang="et">Waveform on lihte visuaal, mis näitab ekraanil kahte signaalikujulist graafikut - üks vasaku ja teine parema kanali jaoks, mis mõlemad liiguvad muusika rütmis.</description>
    <description lang="fi">Waveform on kaksi aaltomuotograafia näyttävä yksinkertainen visualisointi. Toinen on vasemmalle ja toinen oikealle kanavalla ja ne liikkuvat musiikin tahdissa.</description>
    <description lang="fr">Waveform est une visualisation simple affichant deux graphiques de forme d'onde à l'écran. Chaque forme d'onde représente une voie, gauche et droite, et réagit selon le rythme de la musique.</description>
    <description lang="gl">Waveform é unha Visualización simple que amosa 2 gráficos en forma de onde na súa pantalla, unha por cada lateral correspondente ás canles de audio da esquerda e da dereita que se move ó ritmo da música</description>
    <description lang="he">Waveform הוא חיזוי פשוט אשר מציג 2 גרפיים בצורת גל על המסך, אחד לכל ערוץ שמאלי וימני אשר זז לפי קצב המוזיקה</description>
    <description lang="hr">Waveform je jednostavna vizualizacija koja prikazuje 2 waveform grafikona, po jedan za lijevi i desni kanal koji se pokreću u ritmu muzike.</description>
    <description lang="hu">A Waveform egy egyszerű vizualizáció, amely 2db hullámot mutat reprezentálva a bal és a jobb hangcsatornákat, melyek a zene ritmusára mozognak.</description>
    <description lang="it">Waveform è un semplice visualizzatore che mostra 2 grafici di forma d'onda sullo schermo, uno per il canale destro e uno per quello sinistro, che si muovono a ritmo di musica</description>
    <description lang="ja">Waveform は画面に2波形グラフを表示するシンプルなビジュアライザーです。音楽に合わせて、右チャンネル、左チャンネルの波形が表示されます。</description>
    <description lang="ko">Waveform은 간단히 두개의 웨이브폼을 화면에 보여줍니다. 각각 왼쪽, 오른쪽 채널이고 음악의 비트에 따라 움직입니다.</description>
    <description lang="lt">Waveform yra paprasta vizualizacija katra rodo dvi garso bangas ekrane. Viena banga vieno kanalo garsas.</description>
    <description lang="mk">Бранови е едноставна визуализација која покажува 2 брановидни графови на екран, по еден за десниот и левиот канал од музиката</description>
    <description lang="nl">Waveform is een simpele muziekvisualisatie die twee golfvormen op het scherm toont, respectievelijk voor het linker- en rechtergeluidskanaal. De golfvormen bewegen mee met de beat van de muziek.</description>
    <description lang="no">Waveform er en enkel visualiserer. Waveform viser to bølgeformede grafer på skjermen som beveger seg til musikkens rytme. En for venstre og en for høyre lydkanal.</description>
    <description lang="pl">Waveform jest prostą wizualizacją pokazującą dwie fale dźwiękowe na ekranie. Każda na jeden kanał dźwięku.</description>
    <description lang="pt">O Waveform é uma visualização simples que mostra 2 gráficos ondulantes no ecrã, um para cada canal estéreo. Estas ondas movem-se ao ritmo da música.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">O Waveform é um visualizador simples que mostra 2 gráficos ondulantes na tela, um para cada canal estéreo</description>
    <description lang="ro">Waveform este o vizualizare simplă care arată 2 grafice în formă de undă pe ecran, câte unul pentru fiecare canal stâng și drept și care se mișcă după bătăile muzicii.</description>
    <description lang="ru">В этой визуализации отображаются 2 графика для левого и правого каналов, которые движутся в такт музыке</description>
    <description lang="se">Waveform är en enkel visualisering som visar 2 vågformsgrafer på skärmen, en för vänster och en för höger kanal som rör sig i takt med musiken</description>
    <description lang="sk">"Waveform" je jednoduchá vizualizácia zobrazujúca 2 grafy priebehu signálu pre pravý a ľavý kanál, pohybujúce sa v rytme hudby</description>
    <description lang="sl">Waveform je preprosta vizualizacija, ki prikazuje valovni obliki zvoka iz levega in desnega kanala, ki sledita ritmu glasbe</description>
    <description lang="sq">Valëzuesi është një Vizualizim i thjeshtë që shfaq 2 Grafikë Valëzues në ekran, nga Një për secilin kanal, të Majtë dhe të Djathtë, që lëvizin sipas ritmit të muzikës</description>
    <description lang="sv">Waveform är en enkel visualisering som visar 2 vågformgrafer på skärmen, en vardera för vänster och höger kanal som rör sig i takt med musiken.</description>
    <description lang="th">Waveform เป็นการแสดงผลภาพเวอร์ชวลไลเซชั่นพื้นฐานที่จะแสดงกราฟสัญญาณเสียง 2 กราฟบนหน้าจอ โดยเป็นกราฟสัญญาณเสียงซ้ายและขวาตามจังหวะของเพลง</description>
    <description lang="uk">Waveform є простою візуалізацією що показує 2 осцилограми на екрані. Кожна лінія відповідає своєму каналу і змінюється в такт з музикою.</description>
    <description lang="zh">Waveform是一个简单的可视化效果，它在屏幕上显示两个波形图，分别与音乐左右声道的节拍相呼应。</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="weather.wunderground" name="Weather Underground" version="1.0.9" provider-name="Team XBMC">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="2.0.10"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.weather" library="default.py"/>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="resources/lib/wunderground"/>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="af">Weer voorspelling vanaf wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="ar">توقعات الطقس من wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="be">Прагноз надвор'я з wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="bg">Синоптична прогноза от wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="ca">Previsió del temps des de wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="cs">Předpověď počasí z wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="da">Vejrudsigt fra wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="de">Wettervorhersage von wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="el">Πρόγνωση καιρού από το wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="en">Weather forecast from wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="es">Predicción meteorológica de wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="es_AR">Pronóstico meteorológico de wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="es_MX">Pronóstico de wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="et">Ilmaennustus portaalist wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="eu">Eguraldi iragarpena wunderground.com-etik</summary>
		<summary lang="fi">Sääennusteet wunderground.com-sivustolta</summary>
		<summary lang="fr">Prévisions météo fournies par wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="gl">Predición meteorolóxica de wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="he">תחזית מזג האויר מאת wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="hr">Prognoza vremena od wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="hu">Időjárás előrejelzés a wunderground.com-tól</summary>
		<summary lang="is">Veðurspár frá wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="it">Meteo fornito da wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="ja">wunderground.com 天気予報</summary>
		<summary lang="ko">wunderground.com 날씨예보</summary>
		<summary lang="lt">Orų prognozė nuo/iš wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="mk">Временска прогноза од wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="nl">Weersvoorspelling van wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="no">Værvarsel fra wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="pl">Prognoza pogody ze strony wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="pt">Previsão meteorológica a partir de wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Previsão do tempo por wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="ro">Starea vremii de la wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="ru">Прогноз погоды с сайта wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="sk">Predpoveď počasia z wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="sl">Vremenska napoved, ki jo zagotavlja wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="sv">Väderprognos från wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="th">พยากรณ์อากาศจาก wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="tr">Hava durumu wunderground.com sitesinden alınır</summary>
		<summary lang="uk">Прогноз погоди з wunderground.com</summary>
		<summary lang="zh">来自wunderground.com的天气预报</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_TW">weatherground.com 上的天氣預報</summary>
		<description lang="af">Weer voorspelling verskaf deur Weather Underground (http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="ar">توقعات الطقس من تقديم Weather Underground&#10;(http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="be">Прагноз надвор'я створаны Weather Underground (http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="bg">Синоптична прогноза с данните от Weather Underground (http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="ca">Previsió del temps proporcionada per Weather Underground (http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="cs">Předpověď počasí poskytnuta stránkou Weather Underground (http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="da">Vejrudsigten leveres af Weather Underground (http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="de">Wettervorhersage bereitgestellt durch Weather Underground (http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="el">Η πρόγνωση καιρού παρέχεται από το Weather Underground (http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="en">Weather forecast provided by Weather Underground (http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="es">Predicción meteorológica proporcionada por Weather Underground&#10;(http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="es_AR">Pronóstico meteorológico proporcionado por Weather Underground&#10;(http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="es_MX">Pronóstico del tiempo por Weather Underground&#10;(http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="et">Ilma ennustab Weather Underground (http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="fi">Sääennusteet Weather Underground -sivuston tarjoamina (http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="fr">Prévisions météo fournies par Weather Underground (http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="gl">Predición meteorolóxica provista por Weather Underground&#10;(http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="he">תחזית מזג האויר ניתנת ע"י Weather Underground (http://www.wunderground.com</description>
		<description lang="hr">Prognozu vremena omogućava Weather Underground (http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="hu">Az előrejelzést a Weather Underground (http://www.wunderground.com/) szolgáltatja </description>
		<description lang="is">Veðurspár frá Weather Underground (http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="it">Meteo fornito da Weather Underground (http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="ja">Weather Underground (http://www.wunderground.com/) 提供の天気予報</description>
		<description lang="ko">Weather Underground (http://www.wunderground.com/)가 제공하는 날씨예보</description>
		<description lang="lt">Orų prognozė teikiama (pateikiama) iš Weather Underground (http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="mk">Временска прогноза обезбедена од Weather Underground (http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="nl">Weersvoorspelling voorzien door Weather Underground&#10;(http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="no">Værvarsel fra Weather Underground (http://www.wunderground.com)</description>
		<description lang="pl">Prognoza pogody jest dostarczona dzięki uprzejmości serwisu: (http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="pt">Previsão meteorológica fornecida por Weather Underground&#10;(http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Previsão do tempo por Weather Underground (http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="ro">Starea vremii furnizată de Weather Underground &#10;(http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="ru">Прогноз погоды предоставлен компанией Weather Underground (http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="sk">Predpoveď počasia poskytovaná od Weather Underground (http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="sl">Vremenska napoved, ki jo zagotavlja Weather Underground (http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="sv">Väderprognos tillhandahållen av Weather Underground&#10;(http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="th">พยากรณ์อากาศโดย Weather Underground &#10;(http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="tr">Hava Durumu Weather Underground tarafından sağlanır (http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="uk">Прогноз погоди надано Weather Underground (http://www.wunderground.com/)</description>
		<description lang="zh">由Weather Underground（http://www.wunderground.com/）提供的天气预报</description>
		<description lang="zh_TW">天氣預報由 Weather Underground (http://www.wunderground.com/) 所提供</description>
		<disclaimer lang="af">Die gebruik van hierdie byvoegsel impliseer dat U saamstem met die Terme van Diens uiteengesit op http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ar">استعمالك لهذه الإضافة يعني انك وافقت على شروط الإستخدام الموجودة على الرابط http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="be">Выкарыстаньне гэтага дадатку пацьвярджае што вы згаджаецеся з Умовамі Выкарыстаньня што знаходзяцца на http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="bg">Употребявайки добавката Вие се съгласявате с условията за ползване на услугата, които се намират на http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ca">L'ús d'aquest complement implica que vostè ha acceptat els termes de servei ubicats a http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cs">Používáním tohoto rozšíření schvalujete podmínky užívání umístěné na http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="da">Brug af denne add-on indebærer, at du har erklæret dig enig i vilkårene for tjenesten, der findes på http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="de">Mit Benutzung dieses Addons bestätigen Sie, dass Sie den Nutzungsbedingungen auf http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html zustimmen.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="el">Χρήση αυτού του πρόσθετου συνεπάγεται την αποδοχή των Όρων Χρήσης της Υπηρεσίας (Terms of Service) οι οποίοι βρίσκονται στο http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en">Use of this add-on implies that you have agreed to the Terms of Service located at http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es">Al usar este complemento, aceptas los términos de uso de http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_AR">Al usar este complemento, aceptas los términos de uso de http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_MX">El uso de este add-on implica que usted esta de acuerdo con los Términos de Servicio localizados en http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="et">Selle lisamooduli kasutamine viitab sellele, et te olete nõustunud kasutajatingimustega aadressil http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="eu">Gehigarri hau erabiltzeak http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html -en aurkitzen diren zerbitzu baldintzak onartzen inplikatzen du.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fi">Tämän lisäosan käyttäminen tarkoittaa, että olet hyväksynyt osoitteessa http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html sijaitsevat käyttöehdot</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr">L'utilisation de cette extension implique votre acceptation des Conditions Générales d'Utilisation disponibles sur http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="gl">Empregar este Engadido implica que vostede aceptou os termos de servizo localizados en http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="he">שימוש בתוסף זה משתמע שאישרת את תנאי השימוש אשר ממוקמים בכתובת הבאה http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hr">Upotreba ovog add-ona podrazumjeva da se slažete sa Pravilima korištenja koja se nalaze na http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hu">A kiegészítő használatával elfogadod a következő feltételeket: http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html&#10;&#10;    </disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="is">Notkun á þessari viðbót gefur til kynna að þú hafir samþykkt skilmálana sem finna má á http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="it">Usando questo add-on accetti i Termini di Servizio consultabili su http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ja">このアドオンを使うと、http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html にある規約に合意したものと見なされます</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ko">이 애드온을 사용하는 것은 http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html 에 있는 서비스 약관에 동의함을 의미합니다</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="lt">Naudodami šį priedą jūs sutinate(-kote) su paslaugų teikimo sąlygomis esančiomis http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="mk">Користење на овој додаток имплицира дека се согласувате со условите за користење кои се наоѓаат на http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nl">Het gebruik van deze add-on impliceert dat je akkoord gaat met de service-voorwaarden op http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="no">Bruken av dette tillegget betinger at du har godkjent brukervilkårene på http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pl">Korzystanie z tego dodatku jest równoważne z akceptacją regulaminu dostępnego pod adresem: http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt">O uso deste Add-on implica o seu acordo com os Termos do Serviço. Pode encontrá-los em http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Usar este add-on implica que você concorda com os termos de uso localizados em http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ro">Folosirea acestui plugin implică acceptarea Termenilor și Serviciilor aflate la adresa http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ru">Используя это дополнение, вы соглашаетесь с условиями предоставления услуг, доступными по адресу http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sk">Používaním tohto doplnku súhlasíte s podmienkami používania služby umiestnenými na http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sl">Z uporabo vtičnika se strinjate s Pogoji uporabe, ki se nahajajo na http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sv">Användning av detta tillägg innebär att ni har accepterat användarvillkoren som går att hitta på&#10;http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="th">ในการใช้บริการโปรแกรมเสริมนี้หมายความว่าคุณได้ยอมรับเงื่อนไขในการให้บริการโดย http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="uk">Скориставшись цією надбудовою, ви тим самим погоджуєтеся з умовами використання: http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh">使用此扩展功能意味着你同意此连接下的服务条款：http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_TW">使用這個附加元件代表你同意 http://www.wunderground.com/weather/api/d/terms.html 所載之使用者條款</disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="xbmc.addon" version="12.9.2" provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <backwards-compatibility abi="12.0"/>
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.core" version="0.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension-point id="metadata" schema="metadata.xsd"/>
  <extension-point id="repository" schema="repository.xsd"/>
</addon>

<addon id="xbmc.core" version="0.1.0" provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <backwards-compatibility abi="0.1"/>
  <requires>
    <c-pluff version="0.1"/>
  </requires>
</addon>

<addon id="xbmc.gui" version="4.0.0" provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <backwards-compatibility abi="4.00"/>
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.core" version="0.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension-point id="skin" schema="skin.xsd"/>
  <extension-point id="webinterface" schema="webinterface.xsd"/>
</addon>

<addon id="xbmc.json" version="6.0.0" provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.core" version="0.1.0"/>
  </requires>
</addon>

<addon id="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0" provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <backwards-compatibility abi="1.0"/>
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.core" version="0.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension-point id="scraper.albums" schema="scraper.xsd"/>
  <extension-point id="scraper.artists" schema="scraper.xsd"/>
  <extension-point id="scraper.movies" schema="scraper.xsd"/>
  <extension-point id="scraper.musicvideos" schema="scraper.xsd"/>
  <extension-point id="scraper.tvshows" schema="scraper.xsd"/>
  <extension-point id="scraper.library" schema="scraper.xsd"/>
</addon>

<addon id="xbmc.pvr" version="1.7.0" provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.core" version="0.1.0"/>
  </requires>
</addon>

<addon id="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <backwards-compatibility abi="1.0"/>
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.core" version="0.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension-point id="script" schema="script.xsd"/>
  <extension-point id="subtitles" schema="script.xsd"/>
  <extension-point id="lyrics" schema="script.xsd"/>
  <extension-point id="weather" schema="script.xsd"/>
  <extension-point id="library" schema="script.xsd"/>
  <extension-point id="plugin" schema="pluginsource.xsd"/>
</addon>
</addons>
